From the shadows of the subconscious, to the chaos of the cosmic scrolls, this is Psyche Awakens.
Crowd, whoosh, sparkly chimes, thundercrack, you smooth mystical.
Yo, welcome to the madness, buckle in tight, tear it on deck, third eye in flight, troops get told, he goes unfold, we stir the soul with a tea surf cold, panels be popped.
Trolls be dropping, spirits in the chat and the vibes ain't stopping
Lenore's on guard, tricks bringin' love
Lola, Rudy Marble's fan from above
It's like the Awakens step in the flame
We call your truth, we say your name
It's wild, it's real, it's so big play
Now grab your tea and slay the dead
It's like the Awakens, don't look away
Your shadow's talking, it came to stay
We laugh, we cry, we speak
We scream, live from the madness
This ain't no dream
So you know who that was, you can hear his dumb laugh.
Oh, well, I mean, go ahead, it's like,
he really poured him on music a thousand times,
and I'm still here.
Hi Jamie
Yeah, I mean eventually I'm gonna have so many like members that I'll just do members only streams
I'll do more members only streams, but
to a few now.
Jenny girl, Jen Jen, you've got a membership.
Gina Thomas, congratulations Gina Thomas. I'll do one more
And taco
Taco has received a membership. Hopefully I'll see these people in here
Yeah, I guess that they do say that you are on the first of the month you are given some memberships to give out
But those are not you that those you won't receive monetization for them. They'll just they're just free memberships
Always perform body when six around home. Yeah, I know it was though. It was what's his name. I won't even say his name
But you know AMC
It's the only porn bomber that goes yeah
He's like the only guy left at the concert, you know at the end after everyone's like sing free bird again sing free bird
Hi
Guys, if you're not opted in to receive a free membership,
a gifted membership, they are available.
If you click on the word says one gift above,
you can either gift memberships or you can opt in
to make sure you're opted in to receive a membership
when they are given away.
Click the little gift icon at the top of the chat.
Make sure you're opted in
and you're eligible to receive a membership.
So we have three new members.
We have Jenny girl, Jen Jen, we have a taco
The last person was
It was Gina Thomas, okay. Oh my god, it's always big
big
Not in the mood to have a guess on right this second, but I'm gonna wait for the chat to build up a little bit
Okay, I
Think I'll do more of like the narcissist book
We live in an epidemic of narcissism in this country, HG Tudor.
So this book is about, by an actual narcissist that tells his thought process.
His name is HG Tudor.
He's really a lot of books on HG.
Oh my gosh, this keeps correcting my Tudor.
He's correcting my grammar.
Okay, so this is called the Devil's Toolkit. So this one is from the Devil's Toolkit and it says all these like little tools that they use
but they put them into like, you know, the power tools.
So it says
the first we have the
Okay, so first we have the saw of interruption and then we have the chisel of misery. I think we read of that and we read
Okay, so then we have the hammer of intimidation
Then we have the
Screwdrivers of diversion says I have made mention of how we cannot stand to be criticized
This is something which strikes at our very core and causes us great pain
It can bring about our destruction and we must ensure that any criticism is dealt with in a similar vein
We do not allow you ever to gain the upper hand with us to allow you to do so might give you too great an encouragement
To challenge us and that is not something we can confidence
You must know your place. Your place is beneath us, and you must be kept there.
One of the most effective ways of keeping you in your place is by denying you the opportunity to be right.
You cannot be right because we are always right. It is a necessary consequence of our
superiority and also results of the fact that we created reality different to yours or your rules do not apply.
It is our rules of logic that reign supreme in this altered world, and this means we are always always right.
Notwithstanding this you still insist on trying to apply the rules of your world to our interactions
We find this highly irritating
But as always in the case we see this as an opportunity to turn the tables on you and extract fuel from you
Should you be trying to explain something to us and you do so in a temper or upset?
We are content for you to continue in this vein your emotional response provides us with fuel and unleashed
And at least is what we decide, we wish to increase your emotional input and thus improve
the quantity and quality of the fuel that flows from you.
Then we are content to leave matters be.
Instead, you try, if you decide and try and put a straight in this irritating manner of
yours by doing so in a common reason manner, then we have to delve into our toolkit once
again.
You have this unending need to be proved right.
I've seen it many times.
In fact, I do not think it is actually so much
about proving that you're right.
It is more about showing us that we are wrong.
You are unable to accept that the rules of engagement
have been created by us,
and therefore they are bound to favor us.
You are unable to comprehend this.
Instead, what you do is decide
that there must be something wrong with us.
How is it that someone like us, intelligent people,
are unable to grasp the force of what you are saying?
It does compete with you and you repeatedly attempt to get us to see that we are incorrect
and you are correct.
You will not rest until you've achieved this.
Since you engage in this practice in a calm and level-headed manner, then it infuriates
us because you are using up our time and not giving us any fuel.
Which is deliver without any emotion. We are being deprived of fuel
You're also keeping us from going and getting it from somewhere else
This will not do we must stop what you're doing and bring about the resumption of the supply of fuel
To do this we reach for our screwdriver of diversion
The screwdriver has a grip that has been fashioned so it is only usable by us
Nobody else can utilize a screwdriver if they happen to try and do so all that would do is spin around in their hand without achieving anything
The grip is such that our hands fit perfectly and enable us to apply a twisting motion
which brings about an efficient turn at the end of the screwdriver.
We will apply the screwdriver at any given situation in order to twist it.
This twisting might be done to confuse you or to make what you are saying demonstrative
of our superiority. What you say to us will be subjected to the screwdriver and twisted
so that it no longer resembles what you first intended. This is the most effective as it will
invariably cause you to become irritated, frustrated, and annoyed. A careful application
enables us to take a common-placid conversation and twist it into an argument within a few moments.
As usual, by turning everything around we will cause you to lose that implacable expression
and instead you react and feed us with fuel. The screwdriver comes with two adjustable ends
which can be fitted easily and used straight away. The first end is the denial. This enables
us to avoid any allegation that you'll be leveling at us. You may believe that your assertion of some
perceived wrongdoing on our part is based on a solid foundation of logic but a few twists with
and we were able to justify how you are wrong
and we have not actually done anything wrong.
The denial end on the screwdriver is made
from reinforced belief
and has consequently almost indestructible.
As such, the use of denial when wielding the screwdriver
means that no matter how forcefully an assertion is made
and on what might appear to be the strongest grounds,
it is easily twisted to one side
by a few turns of denial tips screwdriver.
It is also useful at taking apart any evidence that you might advance in support of your
argument.
For example, if you accuse us of sending text messages to another lady and present a telephone
message bearing such messages, we will just keep turning the screwdriver a few times and
undo your argument by repeated denials.
You will keep pointing at the telephone, but DOSA has rendered useless and shows nothing
but use of denial tips screwdriver.
If you present a document, then a few turns of the screwdriver will result in this document
being worthless as it is shredded by the screwdriver's action.
The second end, which can be applied to the screwdriver of diversion, is the blame shift.
This particular tip slips readily onto the end and is good to go in all situations.
A few turns of the screwdriver and it enables us to deflect your arguments and allegations
by demonstrating how you are at fault.
We turn the screwdriver and the rest of the argument is turned around as we shift the
blame onto you.
For example, you might be chastising us for turning up late and smelling of perfume and
alcohol.
We have applied the denial to the screwdriver and given a few turns, but you have persevered.
You will not stop pointing out that we've smelled some ladies' fragrance in a brewery.
Accordingly, a quick change of tip, and we apply this to whoever once again.
If you show more affection, I would have not have to go out, would I?
What? You just denied you've been out?
No, I did not. You're trying to change the topic because you know you are in the wrong.
What are you talking about? You are the one who's wrong here.
You came in at 3 a.m. and smelled some whore.
Perhaps I do but it would not have happened if you put him put out more often. Oh, so it's my fault is it glad you agree
When did I say I agree? You're trying to blame me. I'm not trying to blame you. I'm blaming you
I am blaming you. You do not give me any attention anymore. I'm starved of affection
Is it any wonder I want to have a few drinks and enjoy the company of somebody who actually pays me some attention?
I do pay you attention and plenty of it
I'm always doing things for you if anyone has started with tensions me stuck in here at night
whilst you get about
There you are, all about you again. Jesus, do you ever think of anyone other than yourself?
What do you mean? How on earth can you say that after everything I do for you?
That's a joke. I'm the one who works hard to keep this house and pay for everything.
That's only because I have to care for the children.
That's easy. You want to try and do what I do. It's damn hard work,
but you wouldn't care about that, would you? You're not interested in me.
Yes, I am. I always ask how you dazed them.
And so on it goes, a few twists of the screwdriver
and the blame shifts attached,
and you have stopped attacking and accusing us
of staying out late and you are now too busy
defending yourself to respect our allegations,
and respect our allegations.
It is a very useful device for turning a situation around
and putting you on the defensive,
all with a required provision of fuel also.
It says, each screwdriver of diversion
also comes with a complimentary set of screws you down.
These hardened screws made from the toughest malice
are used by the real professional.
They only fit with the blame shift head of the screwdriver and are used when the tables have been turned and we have placed you in the back foot.
Once that has been done, the screws you down are applied. Each of these screws is driven into you by the screwdriver and reinforces our argument, leading you with nowhere to go.
You are invariably so staggered at the force of our argument, so perplexed at how we have managed to outflank you, that these small yet beautiful screws are applied to pin you down just so you can be subjected to further belittlement and denigration.
We keep you just where we want you.
You have no opportunity to get away
and we are able to reach into our toolkit
for a different tool to use on you
for our benefit and your detriment.
So there we go.
That is the screwdriver of diversion.
We have juice to show, okay?
And thank you juice.
I'll never see you again
because it's not the real juice to show.
Good try though.
Good try.
Hey guys.
Do you like that you like that chapter though? That was pretty interesting. It's like, you know, you'll notice that
You know, if you might have something to bring to them and then they're all of a sudden it's on you. So
It's called a screwdriver of diversion
We're back guys
Okay guys
I'm gonna give you some names guys. Is anybody a content creator that gets porn bombed?
I can give you three names right now of porn bombers, and they're real names
If you would like me to
Call them out. Now. What is the next day? She says yo, yo, yo, is you reading today only?
Hmm nice nice. I'll be right back
Does anybody want to know the
porn bombers names I can get I'll give two that I gave yesterday
There's a porn bomber named John Woo. There's a porn bomber named
What's the guy Ben and ramen?
Okay, those are two names. I'll give the third one of someone asked, but I'm not gonna tell somebody else
If you see those names you're probably being porn bombs you can thank me later
The only thing that works on me now is that putting somebody that I know know and so but that I recognize the names and so I
Think I have it all squared away now. I'm not just gonna bring people up anymore. I'm just gonna
Be very careful about that
Because if they don't do the poor bomb they'll do the n-word bomb
It's not a big deal, but I don't want it right now, so
Okay, since the people leave in the room, so I'm just going to continue reading.
Find a short chapter.
Rose, so this is called, this is by the way, this is from a book called The Devil's Toolkit.
It's a book about narcissism written by narcissists, and he's talking about the tools he uses
manipulate. And so it says rose-tinted spectacles. This pair of spectacles will
be my first gift to you. You'll become familiar during the seduction phase that
we do enjoy buying you gifts. We usually do this using the resources of the
person we have just got rid of. Goodness me, was she crazy? Thank the Lord. I
realized in time what a psycho she was and it got rid. I will tell you about it
as I recount my lucky escape. Hey Nancy!
We like to use the resources of others because we are entitled to do so, and we are able
to use our scissors of sniffing, see below, to cut through the boundaries which you put
in place.
Your money is our money.
Our money is yours.
I'll be writing in the future about the narcissist's relationship with money, but that is for
another occasion.
Thus, we hand you a pair of these spectacles, and you will always have to put them on.
We most likely have hurled a hand-grenaded gratuitous affection, see below, and add to
you, and you are stunned by this torrent of affection.
spectacles on you. It may be really from a volley of our nail gun of flattery so that you may be
unaware we have given you these glasses.
Once once on you will look at us favorably and always see what we're doing in the best light
You love everything that we do our gestures are generous and loving we look fantastic to you
And you fall head over heels in love with us the spectacles work their magic by ensuring that whatever you whenever you look at us
You will only ever see good things
It may have been constructed this effect only works in conjunction with looking at us
If you look on someone else the tint fades and you are just looking at them through ordinary glasses
By placing these spectacles on you, I'm able to make you think I am wonderful so that you miss warnings and you overlook certain problems.
It certainly makes my life easier that when I've been able to make you wear these spectacles.
Of course, you get to benefit from wearing these glasses because you feel happy and content since everything looks wonderful to you.
There is nothing you need to be concerned about.
Even if it's some interesting interfering idiot,
trots along and tries to persuade you to the contrary when you look at me whilst wearing these glasses, you will see
Still see that everything is glowing and perfect.
You will therefore ignore what the person has to say
and quite right as well.
New York is now prosecuting P-bombers with sex crimes.
Wow, that's interesting.
I would love to be able to track the IPs
of some of these people and prosecute them
because they don't know if there's children watching
that they're subjecting this nudity to some guy's dick.
You know, it's like that's not appropriate on YouTube and it's definitely like some kind of like, you know
Assaulting people with something they don't want to see it is actually a crime. It is actually a crime. I think it's disgusting and
That'd be great if the porn bombers could be put in jail great
Anyway
We'll continue on this chapter. It's pretty good. This is the rose colored glasses, right?
And do we wear these sometimes and have they've been put on us without us even noticing sometimes? Yes.
Unfortunately, the longevity of these spectacles needs to be approved. The tint never lasts long enough and eventually fades away.
I'm not able to replace the tint and it always seems to be the case that the rose tinting fades away by the time you let me down.
I'm forced to devalue you. The world no longer looks like it once did and I have to use other devices in the hooper section of my toolkit
but I want to make you feel wanted and happy again.
It is no great matter since I enjoy using these Hooper devices, but ultimately it would make my life easier and I'm all for that, of course, if the tint would last longer.
I'm unsure as to why it fades in this manner. I suspect you must be something to do with it as everything is usually your fault.
I do know that you are not able to take the spectacles off and you must do something to the lenses.
I should imagine that you rub at them or something so that the tint is affected it becomes diminished.
I did wonder whether it's because I have been staring because I have used staring at my golden
radius for so long it might burn through the tint and that's when the glass is useless.
I gave that some consideration but came to the conclusion that it cannot be the reason because
that would mean that I am at fault and that never happens.
Hopefully the next time I can verse with the boss down below
He will come up with an improved set until that time
I will just have to keep using my other tools of seduction and hoovering. There you go. Oh
Why did everyone leave?
Shit not good
Well, it might be might be might be a
Shadow band because of all the form bombing. Okay. Bye everybody
I finished
So I guess you don't like when I read huh
But everyone leave everyone everyone just tick off. Oh, yeah, it's only I think we're alone now
It doesn't seem to be anyone around
Maybe it's my glasses
It kind of makes me think that there maybe there's some narcissist or something that got scared away by having their tools revealed
But yeah, if you want to see the cover of the book, I'll just show you the cover of it
It's called the devil's toolkit. It's by HG Tudor. It is a great book. There's a cover
The Devil's Toolkit by H.G. Tudor.
A good book on Amazon is from the Knowing the Narcissist series.
But I do find that narcissism is an epidemic in the United States now.
It used to be like a 2% of the population, kind of like psychopaths or extreme narcissists.
Pretty much about everybody in California is
It's kind of like part of survival. Even I have to be a little bit of a narcissist in order to have an if ego to survive
Or else
You'll be chewed up and spit out here in Los Angeles or California or anywhere else
So let's do a collective reading for the chat
You might relate to this you may not but let me know if you'd like a private read or a you know a
Personal reading and then I'll do one full of you some cards in the chat, but let's these
Yeah, I can shuffle actually these are actually easier to shuffle. Oh, there you go. There we go popped out. Oh shit
Page of swords pages swords. So there's been somebody watching you. This is a spy
This is maybe not in a bad way.
Maybe it's somebody just checking your progress
and checking on you.
If it was outside data, I would say
there's a definitely a criminal spy.
This is more like, hey, do a criminal background check
or just watch when they come in and out.
They're looking over some kind of like,
almost like blinds, almost like looking through blinds
a little bit.
Okay, hey, Halo, how are you?
Okay, so we got that one.
That just popped out. So I think there's somebody watching you, but maybe not in a bad way, you know, don't take conclusions
Well, here we go, King of Pentacles coming into your some kind of power where you're where you're in abundance
Or somebody to help you with a lot of abundance that will help you with some kind of idea
They can maybe finance you or be a sponsor or a patron
Okay, there's somebody so wealthy person you may be stepping into this energy yourself of just being abundant and
You know just things are coming to you
But this is like the master of the law of attraction and things just come to this person
Okay, so there's always a good person to know they can help you manifest as well. What else we got for the chat
Random guy hold on
Let's take it
Did you really need to do all that yeah, I did just to make sure I get I've got poor bomb twice already
Oh, you know one time. I guess yeah. Hey, how are you? Oh, I'm good. How are you?
So you got end bomb the other day and like your response was to what go shave your beard like how does that even like add up?
Like what's the correlation? You're like, oh shit. My stream's getting torpedoed. I'm gonna go shave real quick. What?
No, it was I got I think because I think because my beer was looking a very gray
And then it's like on tiktok when I was streaming I like, you know, it's like a lot of people were just like streamed like that
Flip by me, you know how do you kind of like doom scroll?
They were just scroll by me because I was like probably too too old-looking and I like my story better
Yeah, maybe well your story is made up though. My story is the true story. I didn't really it wasn't made up though
I mean the timeline matches up it doesn't because I shaved right after I got off of tiktok not off of YouTube, so
No, no, no, you got torpedoed you're Joe Shirley and bombed you okay, and then you shut the stream down
You want to go shave you said yeah, I said I had enough of this life. I'm gonna go shave this beard
I can't take this anymore. I
Shut the stream off it. Okay. Well, maybe yes, you're right. You're right. What happened dude, okay?
Well, I'm saying anything else. Hey, you're your friend. Okay. Okay. You're my friend. Okay. Yeah
You're always welcome. Bye later. Bye
Oh not working. Hold on
Hi, you know, what's up
Uh-oh
Hey, bro. Don't call me Tiro bro. Just call me auto or call me firefire. Don't call me I apologize. I apologize
I'm sorry. Sorry. Sorry. So it's a psych or it's a psyche
You can call me psych PSY. It's like actually it's psyche is the goddess and so I say psych is the male version of it
I'm just gonna call you psych. Yeah, you can be psych. Yep
I then okay, bro. Just call me out. Oh fire fire. I got it. Okay. I apologize. Okay. I won't do that
I'll make a mistake again. I forgot
Gotcha. Gotcha. You know, yeah, perfect
Good to see you. How are you today?
I'm doing okay, bro. I'm doing okay fucking hottest fuck out here. It's hot. Yeah, it's well
It's kind of overcast here in Los Angeles. It's like a nice nice day, but yeah, you look like you're sweating a little bit out there
Yeah, I was just downtown. There was a there's some festivities going on and shit, you know like some fucking
salsa dancing and you know, you know what it is
There's some you know a little bit of Latino stuff going on here in downtown London, Ontario
That's where I'm from. I'm I'm in London. Okay, London, Ontario
So is there is there a Latino holiday or something or is it a special occasion?
Yeah, I say every summer bro. It's non-stop
Festivities downtown, you know, well, that's great. It seems like you have the evil you have a large community of Latinos there
Oh, yeah, man. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah
Oh, yeah, it's down. He gets down bro. He gets down bro, you know, cool
Well, I love the cheers. I love Latino people actually good
You don't know me. You don't know me, but I but I guarantee you about
60% of your audience they fucking know who the fuck I am
Okay, guys, you know who I'm auto is guys
Because of sassy scarlet knows who you are. I think Ilya might says and I'm not sure
Halo I say 60
Yeah
60% of audience know me. Okay. Okay
Where where do you where you both well known from where do you go where you go?
What uh shows
I'm not gonna fucking mention. Well fuck I came from bro. You figure it out
Okay, well, I've never I've never seen you before no one in the chat seems to know but
If you do know guys shout out and like let me know so I can get some idea of how this guy's so famous
Auto, okay. Yeah, I'm just
I'm not gonna fucking say well fuck I came from bro. You know what it is
Okay, okay. Well, you know some people like to some people don't I don't know if you wanted to plug plug any shows or anything
So it's fine
So ha so a your bro if you don't mind how old are you?
I'm 42. Okay, but the same age. You know, so you're like, you know 1983 or something like that maybe one
Yeah, and I was just I was listening to you. I was listening to you
I got this
You said it's the same about gray hair, bro. Hey, don't be ashamed of your gray hair, bro
You know what that means, bro, you know what that means
Your experience would be a shame of your gray hair man. Hey
Yeah, I'm not yet. No, you look good. Yeah, you look good. I cuz but it's like I'm on me
It looks kind of I look like you know
I'm like a hundred years old because it's like it's just like my beard turns Santa Claus color
It's like just like right here. I just happened this year. So I'm a little bit still maybe insecure, but I
Like to look a little bit younger, but I'm 44. So how do you think I looked?
No, no, no, you're fine. You're fine to me. I mean, you're good. Okay. Okay. Good. Thanks
Well, some people look to see you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you
I'm wearing glasses too. So it's like I like my glasses, but I might look a little bit different than I normally look
You see I look a lot different
Yeah, I kind of need them to be smoking on some cigarette me about my fight, but no, no
I'm outside, I'm always outside and I got Wi-Fi at home, you know, I got in at home and shit, but
I don't get home until later at night and those who don't know it, you know, those who know me,
they know the fuck, they know what the fuck it is. I don't get home until later at night,
you know what I mean? I'm outside, I'm outside all the time, you know what I mean? So sometimes
I understand. No problem. You're pretty good connection today. So, I do apologize. It's okay. I do apologize if my Wi-Fi pops around. I do apologize ahead of time ahead of time.
No problem. You're a good guest and I enjoy your interview.
Uh-huh, yes. Sike.
Yes. Yes, sir. I hear you. Yeah? I hear you.
Please tell me that you got spirituality in you, because spirituality is different than religion.
You do know that.
Absolutely.
Yeah, and I always will describe myself as spiritual but not religious.
I have a connection with the most high, but I don't necessarily believe I have to follow what a book says to have a relationship with the most high.
I can have my own relationship.
and believe and yeah I think religion is basically just to control people it's
like a it's like a programming to control society and so everyone can have
their own relationship with the divine what do you think you really do that
Listen, I'm a spiritual person. I'm not perfect. Okay. Nobody will ever be perfect on this earth. Okay, right?
That being said, I'm I'm just a human being but I do right what I have inside of me. It's it's fire
You know everybody everybody asked me why the fuck fire fire?
It's because the fire within me, you know what I mean the fire within me means
spirituality not religion
spirituality
Yes
And are you a fire sign? Are you with your astrological sign? Are you a fire sign or?
Does your chart make much sense to your personality?
So you're Aquarius.
27th, 1982.
That makes me Aquarius.
Yes, Aquarius.
I'm a Capricorn.
I'm Aquarius Moon.
Aquarius Moon.
Aquarius.
And so, uh-huh, yeah.
I'm an Aquarius Moon and Aquarius Mars in the first house.
And so that's very much part of my identity.
Also, Capricorn Sun and Capricorn Ascendant in the first house.
So they're kind of different like they're kind of opposite signs, you know, the Aquarius is very can be very emotionally
Emotionally a little bit distant like because they're almost like the aliens. They like that. They kind of see
Everybody's side they they're kind of like but they're kind of above the humanity part of it
They they can be a little bit emotionally cold sometimes because they look at things like it maybe like an alien
We look at the world like a gray
Who are known to be kind of
kind of like it's not too strong with the human emotions, but
Well, yeah, I do understand all that. I understand
No, because um, you know, I'm 42 years old. I'm not 20
First of all, so I I have I have lived a little bit. Okay. It's like I have lived a little bit
I've never been a house cat. I've never been a house cat. I've always just fucking
My thing, you know what I mean? Yeah
Just do what the fuck I want to do. I don't let nobody tell me what to do
You're like the Tomcat you're like the Tomcat you like it's the fuck out of the house and go look so pussy, right?
That's what my cats do my male cast they they come back for like a week at a time and then they're yeah
Yeah, yeah, but yeah
Yeah, yeah, no, no, um
listen, I am
Thing about me is I just like to live life and live life to the fullest and
Yes, that's the wrong thing to do then that's one thing I'm gonna have to learn on my own
Well, I think that we are supposed to be living life as a gift
Yeah
But in my opinion I think it's best. I
Think it's best for certain people
For certain people to just live life
Alone, you know, I mean just go with the breeze
Go with the flow
Sure, it's probably like yeah, I think I think routine. I think routine. It's not good for
Well, you know, like when people are in prison they follow a very strict schedule and they kind of thrive in on that schedule
And if I think the schedules messed up or different they kind of like don't know what to do
You know, it's like and so some people are good with the schedule or be good with the routine and some people are just more wanting to
Go out and experience everything and try all different things and sometimes we'll go through different phases where we one or the other but
You know, I like to stay at home a lot, but I find I can socialize on the internet and I like that, you know
But it's easier than
You know, you can't get as heard as much as in real as in real life dealing with people
Know when you're dealing with people online
in certain ways
Yeah, yeah, I mean if it works for you and that's what you want to do and if it feels right for you
Then go ahead and do that. You know what I mean? I do what feels right for me. I'm gonna be outside all
day
Right summer and winter you name it. I'm gonna be outside because that's that's that's what I like to do
As long as they're not as long as people are hurting other people
I think they should be able to do exactly what they want to do as long as like there's long as there's no
Buddy being hurt in the process then have the freedom to explore the world and to enjoy the world
But don't hurt anybody don't
Don't have malice and just try to just be concerned about your own life and like you know
I'm really into people minding that minding their own business and worrying about themselves, right?
I like the United States is good because we have, you know, like a lot of
Hey, yo, bro, I'm fight for one bro. I'm gonna keep it real with you. You know, I mean, okay
I'm gonna keep it real with me cuz everybody knows who a fuck I am anyway
So if I try to fucking lie, then I'm gonna fucking said it said it straight. I
Mean, you don't know me but a lot of people know me around this bitch. You understand me, right? Yeah, I
Understand you
That's how summer is
No, no, it's like this. Oh, yeah, that's that's for a guy that's kind of considered a little bit shorter
But it's all how you carry yourself. I think you carry yourself
the same as anybody so
No, that doesn't really matter how tall people are. I'm very tall. I'm six foot three
So I'm taller than everybody pretty much, you know, so
Oh, yeah, that's that you're tall bro. That's like way average. That's you're tall as fuck
Six foot three. Yeah, all the guys in my family are six foot or taller. My dad was 62
I'm the tallest though my family though and skinny. Yeah, very skinny
Very skinny
Fuck you so fucking skinny look at your arms
I've always been the skinny. I always have been like since I was when I was like a baby
I had this thing where I had to get the operation on my esophagus because I could not hold food down
I would throw up everything I ate and so I've since then I've been skinny all my whole life. I think and
I will all the
When I wanted a time I'll be on stage one more time. Okay. I could do one at a time on stage. I'll be someone's back
Someone's backstage. I'm sorry
Yeah, but so how's your day? Did you have a nice? See what is it today Sunday? Do you have a nice weekend? You're working today?
You have
Anorexia
Well, it's like yeah, I don't I don't have I don't have any kind of eating problem. I just I'm just kidding
Sorry, go ahead.
Oh, I think I lost him.
Auto?
Okay, come on, come on back Aldi.
I think I'm losing him.
Okay, come on back.
Oh, here we go.
Okay, back.
Here we go.
Oops.
There we go.
Better.
It might work better I
His wife
Fuck around in the Wi-Fi fucks around it
So so like every time you eat you you you you you get sick
No, I don't know that's when I was a baby able to get away does when I was a baby, but now now it's just like I'm just skinny
I'm not like some money hungry anyway, but yeah, I'm gonna tell you I was gonna let you back in if you behave
But you're not behaving and so I'm about to kick you off again. Yeah, I have to sponsor panels
I'm not gonna do panels and then then everybody's out of luck, right? It's not weird. Yeah, cuz I'll have one at a time up
Anyway, he's gone. So
It's not weird. Oh here we go. Sorry. I'm back
Yeah, I don't know
I've always been skinny even like when I worked out I worked out I got I got some muscle tone
But I like really didn't gain much weight. It's hard. It's hard for me. I don't have that but that big of an appetite
and so I
I've always been skinny always
Yeah, shoot
You know
You know, it's like I have a I have a problem because uh when I go home
Usually when I get home it's like around
11 11 30 a night late and I'm wasted as fuck
You know, I just want to fucking you know, I just want to fucking take all these fucking clothes off and whatever and they call it
Barbam, but I don't call it barbam. I call it. I just wanna fucking let loose. You know what I mean when I get home, you know
Maybe I shouldn't do that on the internet. You know what I mean?
You said you said you watched porn or what do you say would you get home? I'm sorry what you do when you get home?
No, the people call it poor bomb like they call it that I'm poor bomb. I'm a poor bomb person
I ain't no poor bomb person. I I don't pour bomb nobody bro
I just like to let loose when I get home when I get home and waste it
I just want to let loose. I just want to
You know, I mean, do you do you port mom people though you port mom? You will but you get drunk or something but not
We're not with we're not with the intentions not with the intentions. It's just like me letting loose
See you like you mean you look you look you like we'll get naked or something
Or you show like a video on the screen or you will accidentally take off your pants or something
No, I might be like like I'm right here right now, right?
And then you find my home and it's like 11 30 and I'm wasted. I'm just gonna take my clothes off
I'm just gonna fucking take everything off and just like
In my brain, it's normal, but it's not normal. Okay
Well, yeah, it will be a little like you can call me you can call me on the phone and just poor mom me on the
On the regular telephone. Oh, so you perform our channels several times
Okay, well, I wouldn't really mind you're an attractive guy, you know, I
Wouldn't mind I believe the episode. Yeah, thank you. That's not not to hit on you
I know you're probably straight and stuff like that, but you know, I do find you attractive. I mentioned Latino guy
They they a come on bro come on bro. They okay, you have no idea. You don't know me. It's okay. That's fine, bro
That's fine, bro, but I get laid bro. I get pussy. So I'm not I'm not a desperate fucking dude, you know
It's just
If you ever get naked in front of me, would that be too gay? Would that be would that be gay if you like porn bought me like sometime
Would that be too gay?
I wouldn't give a fuck bro, cuz I don't like I don't give a shit. I just don't give a shit
I just don't care. I mean don't care
Okay, I'm fine fire, bro. I'm out of bra. I'm gonna do whatever the fuck I
If I feel like getting naked, I'll get naked. Okay
Well, I don't I mean it's like if you're doing that already like there's there's websites where you can do that like chatterbait or like, you know
You know different websites you can get and then people will pay you and ship you and stuff. Why don't you do that?
You can make some extra money
Do you mind?
Yeah, you guys you know, you know, I like Hispanic guys, right? Yeah, look at this guy, but it's it's not like
It's not like I don't I don't
It's not like that. I don't do it because I don't I don't know how to fucking explain it
Okay, it's like to do it's like to be not naughty or something like that. It's just like to let loose and have fun, right?
Yeah, I just like to fucking you know get get get a little bit loose and shit like that and not gay
But like loose, you know, I mean, yeah, I want to fucking enjoy life, you know, you want to see this fucking dick here
It is here you have it, you know, I mean type shit
Yeah, so you know, if you do if you do that on if you do that on YouTube then the channel might get in trouble and stuff
And so sometimes they freak out and they get mad at you and stuff
But there's I'm saying there's places to do it. Oh, you understand. I
Understand that because that's against the fucking whatever fucking yeah, whatever
But do you think I understand that when I'm fucking wasted out of my fucking brain
you think I understand that well I've been wasted and I never I never gotten
completely naked I mean I've gotten in my underwear I think on on the show
before but I've never gotten I've never shown anything that that much right but
you know what if you come back yeah I got this fuck huh sorry go ahead no no I
think if you come home if you come home
If you come home drunk one night come on my show and then just let me know when you're ready to do it
And I'll go we get all in the show go back stage and you can show whatever you want
Why what you want to see my dick though you straight no
And I like Latino guys
So you're right up my alley
You are
You know, I heard a lot of women come on this on this fucking channel. Is that true?
Yes, that's true. That's true, but that's why I wouldn't let you poor mom did I don't want the women do with the women to be to be shocked
I mean, but uh
Yeah, we're gonna apply when you're well, you're blasted, right?
You have a lot of beautiful women on the show and but I don't like them to be harassed or like, you know feel like, you know
Uncomfortable at all. So you if you if you harass anybody just harass me. I'm good with it. Okay?
Yeah, yesterday was my first time around here and share around this fucking block
And I saw that walking summer woman and I think she's fucking cool. I think it's a fucking attractive
I think she I think she's a fucking
Yo, I think summer is gorgeous. Yes flower if I if that's the way I see it
Okay, but you can I'm sure she I think that she's she's like she's like, you know
That summer woman, I think she I don't know how old she is but I think she I think she attracted
The summer summer is gorgeous. She is and but she's married. She is married and so I don't think she's available
But you know, she she she knows she's I think, you know, she likes to show her tattoos and you know be sexy, too
You know, I don't but uh, but yeah, she uh, I think she's in a happy marriage
And so probably not interested in anything beyond that so so autos who comes from JC's panel. He'll be over here 24 so well. Yeah
Yeah, I think you're gonna you probably like, you know, I don't think she'd be she'd be offended if you were to say she's beautiful
I think you did say that yesterday and she said just thank you. You know, so she's very
She's okay. She's under I think she understands
Yeah, she said thank you and I think that's the that's the that's the right way to
you know to
The react
To say, you know, I even though she's married or anything or whatever. I did not know but
Thank you. Okay. Well, that's good. That's good. You know, I mean, that's I mean
I wasn't like stuck up about hey, don't talk to me. I'm married. Hey, you know, I mean, she's like, okay
Thank you, you know, I mean, it's all good
Yeah, so, you know, that's called maturity by the way, that's that's that's being like, you know
That's, that's been mature, you know, I mean, that's mature about her, you know, she married, she took a compliment. She said, she said, thank you. That's okay. That's good. You know what I mean?
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah
Sassy said Mary women can take a compliment and that's it. Yeah, it's like, you know
It's just make sure you compliment them and don't go any further than that. You know, it's like then
You know, yeah
You know the fact like, you know, you don't have to fucking be a bitch about it. You know what I mean?
Right
Right. I mean it's like a lot of
There's a lot of women that would take offense to that or were they sometimes it wasn't a big guy wasn't even hitting on them in the first place
They just like to take offense and pretend like they're
Big targets, but so it's all different people, you know, but I have a lot of great people on the show though
Yes, I have a lot of beautiful women a lot of a great
Tractive men like to sassy agrees with you. There we go. I agree auto
So fire fire auto up in here
Don't you think don't you think attitude is everything in life, bro
It's like how you fucking take things and how you react bro. It's everything
Yeah, and you'll get so much with a good attitude. You'll get very far
But if you have bad attitude you can get offended by everything and they you know not want to
You know, I think it's I think you have a good attitude and very uh, you're a smart guy
Yeah, like for example, right summers married and all that right and you know what that's okay. That's good
I respect that I respect that you know what I mean? I respect that she didn't fucking
You know went off on me or you know, I mean and said this and that that is this
All she did was said thank you and we kept it moving, right?
So you say are you single guy are you single?
Yeah, I'm single. I'm single and
I'm single and and I get laid, you know, like I like that. I don't like
Commitment, you know, I don't I don't like commitment. I just like to get laid
Okay, well at least you're honest about yourself with that, you know
You're not gonna like just get married then cheat on your wife a lot, you know, you're at least you're so just glad I'm your bachelor
Yeah, exactly. I don't want to do that to a to another human being to another
Woman, I don't want to I don't want to do that. I'd rather just be honest about it
I'm a very sexual being I like I like I like to fuck I like to fuck women
I like to hit it and quit it. I'm very selfish
I'm fucking very selfish in a way
In a way because because I won't I won't commit I won't commit to a woman
I will not commit to a woman. I will not I will not
Okay, well yeah, but if you know what they're they know what they're getting into then it's like, you know
And everyone's happy I guess it's like, you know people like are looking for something and then you get it
And then it's like you can like part ways and shake hands or whatever and find the next person, you know
different people like
Yeah, I mean come back if you want to if you like if you want to come you wanna have an organ come back if you want
You know I miss yeah, you don't have to fucking you know
I don't I don't have to be there in your hair
24 fucking seven and you don't have to be in my all over me 24 fucking seven
You know I mean it's like yeah, let's get it. Let's get it
We are sexual beings if I'm handsome and you're a good-looking woman
I might want to fucking do something to that, you know, I might want to do something, you know
I want to I want to you know, I want to connect, you know, yeah
I think that's important like everybody should be honest about what they're looking for what they want
So they don't mislead people and stuff like that, but then it's like and then everybody knows what they're getting and then
You know, there's not a conflict
But it's like, you know, if someone's falling in love and then they want you to get married and when you propose you're like
Hey, hey, I'm not like interested in marriage. I just like to have fun and like, you know
Meet people and just be my be a bachelor. You know, that's good to tell people, you know
I'll give you an example and and and those who don't know I'll give you an example
Like not even like two weeks ago, right? I
I was just I was just going home, bro. I was just going home on the bus. I don't drive. I don't drive I
Public transportation type of dude. I don't drive
I was just going home. I was just going home
And you know what I mean this girl right this girl this girl wanted this girl fucking saw me
She liked what the fuck she fucking was looking at. Hey, I took her home
Hey, we agree both of us. She's she was 35. She's 34 years old by the way, and I'm 42, right?
You know, it happened two weeks ago. It happened. I'm not bothering her. She's not bothering me
She's not bothering bothering bothering me back. You know what I mean? Yeah happened. It went down
It went down it happened. That's that
And that's the way I like it and that's the way I like
cool
Well, I like that and that's pretty good. It's like, you know
But I have noticed like nowadays especially like on the internet
It's like I can pretty much like on tiktok. Well, I'm on tiktok
And sometimes I like will send gifts to different people and like most of them are straight guys, right?
And even some of them are have all women in the chat, but they'll still like thank me for sending gifts and stuff like that
So people are more like, you know open-minded about at least like, you know, men are gonna be looking at them women are gonna be looking at them
I don't know. It's like that's kind of good for me
I do like a I do like a straight man
Yeah, man, I think I think the I think the word is attachment
I just don't like attachment because I know I'm not good at it. I'm not I'm not good at it
I'm not good with commitments. I like to just fuck around. You know, I mean, mm-hmm
Well, as long as you're honest about that. Yeah
Hey, I'm sorry psych psych, but people take that the wrong way and they call me selfish. Okay, then I'm selfish
Yeah, it does work. There's worse things to be called, you know, it's like selfish is okay
It's like it because everybody's a little bit selfish and like, you know, we're all ourselves
And so it's like we kind of like, you know, I'll be biased towards our own self and looking but you know, that's just
human right
We're kind of selfish beings. We kind of learn learn to be more giving as we go along sometimes
Yeah, but that's not but what I'm saying is I'm not selfish like in in like giving because I'm the most
I'm a generous person what I'm selfish about is is is is having to commit is having to
To lay a woman get to know me
Because I don't think and that means selfish because because I'm a wonderful man
I know I'm a wonderful man, but I don't want to be a wonderful man
I don't want to I don't want to be a wonderful man
Mm-hmm. You know, I'm so I'm selfish in that way not selfish in every way
No, not selfish in every way like you're
You're generous lover like you like you like to make the please your partner like yeah. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah
I get it so you're just not like you know
You're just not like into like having a commitment and like being attached to somebody like you know like have a strong
What was one person? Yeah, like I don't want you to be getting attached to me
I don't want you to be fucking calling me every fucking hour
I don't want you to be fucking, you know asking me what the fuck you are. What are you doing?
I don't want that from a woman, you know what I mean?
And I'm not gonna do that to a woman either vice vice versa
I'm not gonna do that to a woman either, you know, I mean if I if I fucked you yesterday don't fucking be
Bothering me the next day. Don't be bothering me the day. You know what I mean? Yeah
So if you fall asleep, just get up get up quietly the next morning and drive away
Honestly psych couple weeks ago. I had this fucking bitch, right white girl shit. We fucked
I I made her come you know what she did you know what she did psych she left the same fucking night
She left like a good girl like a good fucking girl. She left the same night
Yeah, everything's all good everything
Yeah
I got you. I hear you say sometimes people will like want to move in like after the first time you have sex
You know, so it's nice to have somebody to understand to you. She's probably a little bit of a player too, right?
And so
As long as you understand each other as long as it's all consensual adults, you know, there's nothing wrong with it, right?
Of course, of course. I mean, I mean like I said, I mean, are we not sexual beings or what?
Yeah
Yeah, we're based on like, you know reproduction and like and like even like, you know, even gays have a sex drive
You know, even though they don't create kids people see we have a natural sex drive in this world, right?
Yeah, so that's where I'm coming from, you know
Without the attachment without the commitment without the make you breakfast type shit, you know, yeah
If that makes me a rude man, if that makes me selfish, then I'm a rude piece of shit then
Well, it is refreshing to hear somebody like tell the truth, you know, and to be honest about what they really want
And it's like instead of like playing games or like meeting people on it
Like it seems like you're very honest and up front with people and that's a good thing
Like you know, I mean like
I'm not I don't I'm not trying to fucking be what the fuck is that fucking word?
I'm not like I know I'm handsome. You know, I mean like women like
Plus I'm a choir. Yes, and they women know my energy. You know, I mean women know my energy, bro
They know what I can do. They know it. They fucking know
You know, I mean
Yeah, I know because I'm an Aquarius moon and it says like in my
Yeah, no, no kids
Never been married. I have had a lot of fucking adventures
And I'm planning to have more adventures until I fucking die and just it's just the way it is. I mean
What do you want me to do? I'm not gonna what you know what I mean? I like it this way
Have you ever had it? I like my life the way the way that it is. Yeah
Have you ever had a threesome?
Never three people never never not just one-on-one never I slept with I slept with
Sisters which means one sister gave it to me and then the other one of course of course because they talk and of course
The other sister was after and so I caught I fucked
As I fucked sisters before I mean like
Twin sisters
Number three some no, they were not twins
Okay, no, no, no never never three time and those sisters
They were not twins, bro. They were six years apart
Okay
Well, it's interesting that not all people can say that they've done that
Not a lot of people can say it how you know not a lot of people can say that a lot of horny ass men around here
That don't get pussy at all. You know, I mean, yeah, that's true. There's the incels nowadays
But uh, yeah, so it sounds like you're having some fun though
You're you're getting laid and you know, you need some interesting people and just like live in the bachelor dream, right?
That's what I that's what I'm all about. I mean if that makes me a fucking piece of shit, then I'm a piece of shit then
No, I don't think so. I think it just makes you know, you're a man. It's like as long as you're honest, you know
And then you're fine. Yeah, we're back live. Hey Nancy. We're here with a really good auto
He's a really cool cool guy. So are you Mexican auto or are you from another area of?
Another Latino country remix from Mexico or no, I
Left I left Honduras when I was 11 years old psych
Honduras. Okay. Awesome. You know what I just said? What did I just say? You said you're left
Honduras when you were 11 years old? Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I heard.
I listen. I'm a good listener. Also, I know how to understand the Hispanic
Yeah, but I would like to you know, you're welcome to come on some night if you're too drunk
Then I'll probably put you backstage with me and then we can
Show me show anything you want
All right, hey, bro
Yeah, I made a truth. Tell me the truth. You straight you straight, right?
Am I straight?
My teeth are straight if straight teeth
Okay, I guess that answer question
Yeah, my teeth are the straightest thing about me. I'm a gay guy. I'm a gay. I'm a gay guy
But I won't go beyond your boundaries if you know, whatever you tell me stop. Hey, no, I'll stop. Okay, I
See how it is. I see how it is
I'll be respectful to you and I won't cross any boundaries, but you know, maybe I test the boundary sometimes if you
But sometimes you might need to say hey, you know, go down and I'll stop okay
I won't disrespect, okay?
No worries, bro. You know, I'm a straight. I'm a straight man. I have never
never never been
Whatever that means, bro. No, no experience. You never know. No, no, no
I have never I have never put anything up my butt
Nothing like that. Oh, yeah
Okay
I'm just a straight man. I like I like vagina
I like I like women energy
Only for a moment and then I like I like them to go away after that
I hear you
It's just they thank you for being honest enough. Yeah, I mean I love I love women too
But it's you know, it's like I like that I you know in a different way. I like
Yeah, I just think they're I think I kind of think they're goddesses. It's a lovely combo. Yeah, this is interesting
I know it's kind of my dream conversation. I like I like to talk like about this stuff. So
Cool guy. So what you're telling me straight?
What are you telling me straight up is that you're bisexual you like women and dudes
I dated a woman once I dated a woman once and I had sex with her
But it's like I'm more attracted to men. I would say I'm like much more like, you know
Maybe like 10% women 90% men so
Yeah, all right, thank you for being honest with me, thank you
Right, I know what I'm doing with right
Yeah, it's all honest
But I want to see when he's I see what it says what what you're well known for whipping your dick out on live panel
Well, I wouldn't care if he did it on my panel
I would just end the show or just go backstage with them and then you know, we could do it back there
You can do it back there and uh, you know, he wouldn't you know site
You know site those people are no
day
They try to make it they try to make it like like that's that's what I like to do
No, bro, it's like here and there here and there when I'm wasted, bro
I'll just get naked. That's it bro. I mean like I'm at home. I
I live I live by my own. I got my own apartment
I'm home. I get home and if I want to get everything
I want to get everything off of me, bro. That's what I'm gonna do
Yeah, just have to be careful when you're on like, you know, YouTube it's like as YouTube has rules and stuff
And you don't want people to be like, you know, like feel like they're porn bombs
You know, you can always like there's free cops sometimes you can go the freak off backstage with people and then do whatever you want back there
But get to be careful with that. I don't want to get my channel ever taken down, you know
Yeah, but that's the thing site like that's the thing site. I'm not a porn bomber. What I am is a fucking drunk
Okay
Okay, I get it
Yeah
I'm sorry, bro, but if I'm on a fucking panel if I go on a fucking panel
Shit goes down then shit then shit goes down
shit
Well, I'm not like honestly, I would I would not mind if you did because
I think you're a attractive guy, but yeah Aldi comes out and shows me his balls and then it's like and then it's a
It's a whole different thing, but yeah
Well, you know what thank you very much
You have always been welcoming. I think yesterday. I think it was the first time I came over and visited
JT told me to come over and fucking this is psych. I was like, okay, let me do that
Okay, well, thank you. Thank you. It's a pleasure talking to you. I hopefully I'll catch you some night when you you know
You get kind of too drunk come on come on my show and we'll have a talk, okay?
All right, bro. Yeah, you know what it is, bro. You know what it is, you know
You're honest about your shit. I'm honest about my shit. I
Lot of women a lot of women come around here and you know, I mean
Not in real life in life, you know, like, you know what it is. I'm not a desperate. I'm not a desperate man
I get it. I get it. I mean, I do get it, you know, I
Got you
But it's just like I like to see flowers. I like to see flowers, you know, I mean, I like I like to I like to see
Flowers and the best way to see them
Sometimes it's on a fucking live stream. You know, it's just good. Yeah
All kinds of fucking vibes, you know, I mean like
Did you ever meet flirty? For example? Oh good example site for them
Excuse no flirty diamonds, you know flirty diamonds flirty diamonds. Have you heard of flirty diamonds?
Flirty diamond, okay, okay, just one just wondering never okay
There she is right there you see you see the screen look at the screen there she is right there
Huh?
Yeah, that's flirty damage. He's Hispanic. I just wondering if you knew who she was
No, you don't see okay here. Yeah, okay
It's not really it's not really her. You know her. Yeah, that's her. Yeah, I know her. She's in the chat right now
You say hi. Yeah, three diamonds. She's pretty cool. You want to come up to say hi flirty you're welcome up
She's pretty cool. She's also known a poor mom accidentally sometimes, but
So, but she's cool. I think it's like yeah
I'm taking a piss, you know what I mean?
But I'm not gonna fucking, I'm not gonna do that on,
you know what I mean?
I'm gonna take a piss, I'm well enough
to just take a piss, sip it up, pour it in,
sip it up and that's it, you know?
Okay, that's fine, you're allowed to.
I didn't see anything.
Yeah, you know, I mean like fuck bro. Um, what was I gonna say? I like to fucking I like flowers in real life
I like flower. I like to see flowers even on the fucking live stream. If there's a real if the real if the real I mean
I don't know man that looks like a like a woman. Okay real
Okay, well, you can be flat flower is that a vagina or is that boobs? What is a flower?
Boobs and nipples. Excuse me. What is a flower? Is that nipples or?
Vagina hey, bro
The flower will be the vagina, bro. I mean come on. Okay
Okay, so you like you like flowers. You don't like it. You know like a cucumber. You like a big flower, right?
I like beautiful flowers. I don't like any sausages. I don't like any cucumbers
I don't like any whatever the fuck
I just like flower. Hold on one second. No. Hello
Hey psyche. Hi flirty. This is flirty diamond. Say hi to flirty diamond
Come right here. There we go
How are you? I'm alright just smoking you know
Yeah, this is diamond
Well, yeah, but but you keep saying site you keep saying diamond what I'm what I'm reading is
flirty
demon I
Think she changed your name because she's dating someone named raging demon and so she changed it for 40 demon instead of 30 diamonds
Yeah, she's a boy friend
The smoke in we out his auto auto is a cool guy of diamond. He says he he might he might flash sometimes if he gets too drunk
I know I might we might all relate to that sometimes. I don't think I've ever flashed, but I wasn't some speedo's recently
Yeah, I'm not afraid to show a little bit, but it was covered it was covered so
So hey, so so Otto's from on Dora's a pretty diamond. You're like you're Mexican descent diamond, right? Yeah, I'm Mexican
Mexican
With what do you think of Otto?
You straight up Mexican like you were born
I'm half white also like I'm Mexican and white
Okay
Yeah
Different you know like
People say hey yo, I'm Mexican. No, I'm not Mexican. I was born in Honduras. I was not born in Mexico. You know, I mean
Mm-hmm. Tell me his
call me latino or me hispanic call me latino don't call me mexican because i was not born in
mexico my parents are not even mexican nothing at all they were both my dad and mom from honduras
so i'm just you know i mean like but it's okay i get it i get it i understand it whatever you
know i mean whatever it always just sounds better if you just call me mexican or whatever but i'm
You know what I mean? Yeah, I mean some people like they care about stuff like that and some people don't
Yeah
You're in Canada, right you're in Canada, they're a floaty demon and I'm single on 42 years old
He seems like a cool, cool guy, like a hard worker, but he's always interested in, in, in, uh, sex, he says, but, uh...
That's not so, um...
Yeah, that's me.
That's me.
Because I'm not trying to fucking get with the girl and promise her something and then and then and then turn around and
You know, I mean, I'm not I'm not promising. I'm not I don't promise anything
I I promise you that I'm gonna give you a good fucking go
That's that's
That's all I can do. I mean at least you're honest to the people that you're dating or talking to or whatever
at least you let me know that I'm just trying to hit it for the one time and that's it.
Hit it and quit it, right?
Yeah, I got it. Hit it and quit it, you know.
Diamond, how's things going with you and Raging Demon?
Things are going well, you know, we're not doing the hit it and quit it type of thing,
but you know, things are going well.
I heard you, like, took over, like, somebody's Discord chat room.
Yeah. Um, Barry gave Reggie and I a hotel room in his server. It's called the boom boom room. And we were given a hotel room.
In that server. But right now, Reggie and even got kicked out of the server.
So they had to they had to renovate the hotel room for somebody else now
Well, you can you can always use my my discord chat. It's open for it for you, so
You come back to my chat
Yeah, it's pretty interesting. So what do you got planned for today auto? What are you doing the rest of the day?
Yeah, so that work or what?
No, bro, I'm not fucking keep on drinking these fucking beers probably
Get some more and then probably make it home around 11 30 12
and
sleep it off and then
There's some things that I cannot talk about
So yeah, I got you. I got you. Okay. Well, great. Yeah
So I don't know the chat the chat's kind of been concerning on me a little bit. She's how did you pour by me earlier?
Just haul the chat you pour by me earlier today. I saw it. That was your name name there, but anyway
Okay
Look what's in front of you and don't fucking pay attention was behind
Okay, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Trust me on that
Okay, okay
Yeah, I already probably where you are
Me
Yeah, yeah
Where you are
Um, I'm originally from Cali, but I'm not in Cali right now
I'm in Minnesota right now. I'm a few hours away. I'm a few hours away from Kate, actually
I don't know Kate. I don't know. Yeah, I mean, I'm a few hours away from Mars. So
cool
Yeah, Minnesota. Yeah, Minnesota, bro. Yeah, I'm in Minnesota right now
I'm on a on a whole tour like
You are what are you doing over there like really like if you want to you don't want to stay it's fine, but if you
I'm making money over here. That's really it
I've been to them. I've been to the mall the mall's biggest fuck
Yeah, it's a really big actually
But we'll be small
Different than California though like
You can't buy alcohol past like a certain time like California. It's like till 2 a.m. Over here. It's earlier
Like there's different times on the weekend and it's just really crazy to me like I'm just going to whatever gas station
I'm buying like a beatbox and such and it's not like that over here
Yeah, it's harder to go
Don't have to go I'm so psych but
You don't have to go into details, but what the fuck exactly did you mean by you making money over there?
I sell ass!
Nice, okay, nice!
Okay, okay, okay, okay!
Yeah, I sell ass, that's what I do for, I mean, yeah.
Or companionship, you know.
How is it different from there to like Los Angeles or like California to Minnesota? Like what's the difference in people?
There's more white people here and like like Habibie's there's a lot of Habibie's over here
And like I know what you mean by Habibie's Middle East
Yeah, yeah, they're just like
Oh my God, I had one try to fucking propose to me already.
I actually, you know, he was like, I want you to be mine.
I was just like, be so fucking thrilled.
Just give me that money.
Get your nut off and go.
Thank you.
Sike.
I think, I think I like, I think I like what's going on.
I think I like what's going on.
Okay.
Cool. Yeah, it's a really cool person. Like, uh, yeah, I've known it's already for a few months now and
Entertaining guests and you know, we had a little get a little accidental porn bomb recently, but you know
I thought my dick on psyches. I went my dick out and I got a timeout for a little bit. Oh
Shit, so you're not really a woman
I mean, I'm trans. I got some titties. I got a dick, you know.
Hey, Frankie.
I'm psych.
You ain't really a woman, bro.
I'm setting ass, bro.
Yeah, but I'm no need...
I'm no need trans as self-ass.
On these yeah, I don't think they're coming in Minnesota, huh? Are they not coming in Minnesota? I think you're a kind of
No, there's a lot of trans people in Minnesota to the max actually, but I'm
Really like I'm like the only like Latina trans hooker
On the websites
Okay, there's just a bunch of like white a bunch of white girls, but like
Yeah, you're like the one of the only Latinas. I know there's not a lot of Latinos get over to Minnesota
It's kind of Canada Canada for that for that for that matter, but he says there's a large Hispanic community there though
So hi guy
Am I am I right or am I right right that you take home or pills to grow those things or no?
Yeah, I pick hormones
Okay, okay
yeah so everybody's on the same page yeah I mean I mean don't hold more pills
don't don't don't give you don't give you boobies boobies yeah they they
Yeah, bro, bro, but do you know how do you know when to stop taking home home pills or like do you just keep
I'm getting off the medication once I get a pussy. I'm getting off the medication. Oh
That's a surgery
Surgery plan right you have a surgery plans. Yeah
So she's gonna get a flower, she'll have a flower soon, you know, she'll have her own flower.
Hell yeah, hell yeah, hell yeah, bro. I'm not I'm not fucking stupid. I'm fucking I'm down here. I'm right here
Stupid bro. No, not at all. Not at all. I didn't mean that I didn't mean like that
I just meant that uh, you know
You're at least like able to talk to people and like some people don't even want to talk to another person or they'll get really weird about it
Yeah
So don't worry about it, bro. Don't worry about it. I I I happen to be a very goddamn fucking
What the fuck is the word?
Machismo machismo
I'm not much I'm not much I'm not I'm not I'm I'm I'm I'm a confident
I'm a confident little fucking Hispanic mother mariachi
Okay, you're from Mariachi. Okay, I like that. You're confident Mariachi
You know what I mean? I know I know what I like, but I can also talk to everybody. It's okay
It's okay. Good. I mean
I mean, why not?
Why not?
That's good because they can some people aren't very under that they're not as open-minded as you
You know, it's like they some people don't even want to talk to somebody somebody else that's like that. Uh, so, you know
Confident yeah, you know what it is
Like I rather I rather people be honest with me then people be fucking pulling my leg
You know what I mean, like I rather just fucking to be honest. I'm good. I'm good
Yeah
I mean, to be honest about it. I'm good. I'm okay. I know what I'm doing with and I'm still here. Am I am I not? Yeah
Yes, yes
That's good. But yeah, I did I do feel like it's like, you know
I'd rather have diamond tell you than the me tell you because I don't yeah, so I think it's it's her place to
I didn't tell him I was trans people be like, oh you're going you're coming on to him
You want him and you're trying to trick him and blah blah blah and I'm just like
No, I don't sorry, but I don't really have one exception for the YouTube world. I guess
Okay, well, that's you know, I'm proud of you for that. You know diamond. I think that's a really good move
I think that's a good move and it's like a I think honesty is the best policy to yeah
Yeah, thank you. Thank you. I do I really do appreciate it and I really do appreciate you as a person
I really do appreciate you. It is what it is. I mean
Yeah, yeah, you're not coming on camera today diamond
What I put a shirt on okay, you know, she's gonna come on camera and it's that kind of thing
Let's let's see this
Let's see
So hey being gay summer
Sike, there's something there's something that I'm gonna have to let you know
Okay, go ahead something I have to go site. Tell me
My intuition my intuition is 100%
I'm a man my third eye my third eye tells me every
Good, okay
That's good. It's good to have be in touch with your intuition
That's like, you know, it's like you have to be pretty much in touch with your feminine side a little bit to be so receptive to that
Yeah, hey, hey, bro
You think I'm gonna be a shame of fucking telling you and everybody that I am touched with my feminine side
I'm not afraid. I am I am in touch with my feminine side. That's why this
That's why this dude over here gets pussy. That's why
Yeah, yeah, I think women do like women too. Oh, there we go
There we have it
Hey, David hey the great hi nice to see you
Nice to see you, Sechky.
So, okay, so everything, I saw water under the bridge, anything that happened last time,
I know you got a little frisky and excited that night, but I know you're going to, your
respect comes from now on.
I was a little drunk.
Okay.
Yeah, she got you showed a little bit too much like Otto says he shows a little bit too much on the live stream sometimes too
You know so, you know a little bit of even I do sometimes right so I miss you too. He man. How are you?
I know you know
He managed 40 diamonds holds told everything so we're all good. We're all good. He man was a little bit worried about
No, I mean, I don't even I don't even know because I I'm forced to see people's comments when I'm on stream
Yard, that's why I know that not personless things stuff like that
Yeah, so
Anyway, it's just a conversation is just like, you know, they're you know, they're just just chatting and everything's just closed
And so there's no no secrets here. Okay guys, we're all we're all good
Secrets make friends
Yeah, you're making new friends
So how did you know this Nicole in the chat? He says Nicole says you call her a transformer
Hey, you know that person
Hey
Hey, you're crazy you crazy demon, you know what I like
Like your smile. You got a good smile. Thank you. I like your smile
You're welcome. You're welcome. You know, you know what it is. I like your smile. You know what it is. Come on, bro
Nice white tea
Do you babe what's wrong with what's wrong with that excuse me
To be honest with you. I have paid but I have paid for real woman. You know me. I'm sorry, but okay
I want me to be honest
Okay. Yeah. Oh, yeah. No, I didn't mean to get too personal, but yeah
I'm not gonna fucking be here bro when I know how some people fucking know me bro
You guys don't know me fucking on me. I'm straight. Sometimes I pay I got it in my contact
I pay but I pay a real woman though. I pay a real woman
She won't she won't suck my dick, bro. Unless I fucking
Robert I'm like, what the fuck and I got a fucker too with a Robert too, you know me
But that's a real woman though. You know what I mean? Yeah, you don't want to get
What I pay what I pay
would i pay to be with crazy demon over here i probably wouldn't because i'm a straight man
and that's just the way it is you know i mean but i do appreciate you but i do appreciate you
i appreciate you crazy i mean this dude is calling you uh uh uh
Freaky freaky diamond freaky freaky diamond or something like that. What the fuck is I mean?
I am proud that you have safe sex and like, you know, you get blow jobs with a condom
That's really good that you're doing your part in this world. And yeah, I
Mean, can I call you crazy demon if I don't think people called you crazy demon before
Oh
Sure, yeah comes whatever
All right, I'm gonna call you crazy DMS. Nice to meet you crazy demon. I'm auto you can call me fire fire
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
The whole yeah
So I think I think it's good that I call you a crazy demon. I think I mean fuck it. Yeah
I'm a crazy demon. I I give good throw
I'm crazy
Hey, hey, you know what I mean bro. Do you think bro? I ain't matter to do you think
To box it to box it I ain't matter to do you think
Hi mad at you. Yep. I like I like uh, I like uh, you talk a lot. Yeah
It's all about fucking
heart
Melody and you know what I mean? I'mma put I'mma put this I'mma put this fucking dick in your face
What you gonna do with it? You know me type of shit?
That's Rudy Rudy Rudy Rudy's out today tricks around got a lot of got those make me got those
Got those
Yeah, I think he froze but he's an interesting guy. I like this guy auto. I like this guy
You're cool guy
I got three cuts, but it's for a reason it's for a reason bro. I have to
It's gonna I'm gonna go down for a little bit, but you know what I mean
My mom died five months ago. I took her fucking cat. So now I'm stuck with three
in my place
Well, that's good that you took your mom
Your mom loved that cat I'm sure
Hey, I have a heart bro, I'm not gonna let those cuts just go and be taken away by the wind no no
You know I mean I took I took they live with me in my place
Yeah, I mean, something happened to me. I have five cats. I would hope my family family members would take them in and take care of the cats like they're
I hope my cats are okay if anything ever happened to me, you know
And that's so your good son good son to take his mom's cat because I know she loved that cat and you're you're helping by taking care of the cats
You so good guy
I really like that
It's all about heart, bro. It's all about heart, bro. I mean I mean
That's it, bro. I mean, that's it. That's it. That's why I got three cuts
That's why
Awesome, but uh, awesome
People I missed mine
No, I'm sorry. Yeah
Yeah, I mean I have five cats
But I've had maybe about at least 12 at once one time when I had the cat had babies and stuff that
They naturally just go to different different houses and go wander the neighborhood. So I got
Left a legacy here of cats forever. I think they're my cat will have descendants in the city a hundred years from now. They'll be their relatives
Wow, so what's we got planned for today diamond?
Honestly nothing really I just I'm kind of boring I just really stay home a lot now and like
That's kind of what I do
But you probably had a you probably had a you probably had a hotel right now, aren't you? No
You say with a friend or something I don't know y'all to tell too much if you don't want to but yeah
Yeah, I'm with a friend. Okay. Yeah, I'm with a friend. I'm like
Yeah, I'm just doing what I'm doing and yeah, I mean she's working out though for sure for sure
That's good. How long are you just be saying there?
Um, I don't really know yet cuz like I'm actually like really shocked. It's like I'm doing really well here like in Minnesota like
Like I'm actually doing a lot better here than I was doing in California when it comes to online stuff and like I
Guess until like the money dries out over here
hmm
Okay, good. You still got your place. You got your place to come back to you in LA. Yeah
I still have stuff secure no matter where I go, but like, yeah, right now, money's low
here, and I mean, I want to travel the world and see new states, and, yeah, so.
Well, it's good.
You can meet people online, and then, like, you know, people, you know, like, hopefully
make some friends and be able to go out.
Yeah, you're good
What else auto anything else auto a little bit
I want to ask Chris demon a question. Okay, go ahead. Okay. What?
All right, it is what it is right so, you know, I'm an open book kind of kind of
A lot of people have seen this fucking animal or whatever animal that I am or whatever
But would you consider?
Would you consider six inches small or okay?
I mean it's
Six inches and it's and it's thick it's thick and it's okay
He's five foot one diamond. He's five foot one
Yeah, and I'm five foot one
I mean six inches is good for some people
But not for you
No, for you. I like for you. I like top inches
Two of you, two of you, that is an L equal 12.
I like the foot long, like I like big dick and I mean this average I mean it's better
than like being smaller than six inches like I mean so like I mean at least that yeah at
least you're six inches at least that's solid but girls like me we like big dick
All right, okay. Well, if you like well, oh, I mean one foot long. I mean that's you right?
Yeah, I I like riding the whole rodeo, you know
Like when it when it's a small dick like you can't really be bouncing on it and riding it and shit
When it's a small dick like when it's a big dick you can be like you can be going ham and shit, so
Yeah, you can do that world store, baby.
World store.
Oh, God.
Yeah, world store, you know.
I'm not worried bro, you know, I just got fucking late, you know, I mean like a couple weeks ago, and I'm always I'm always getting it
I'm okay with it. You know, I mean she came
Some guys know how to fuck like when they don't have a big dick like some guys are the big dick
Don't know how to fuck some guys with a small dick know how to fuck. So I mean it does vary but like
Know cuz like even if a guy has a big dick and he doesn't know how to fuck at least I could like hop on top
Do my thing and then be like bye?
And like you know at least I'll still be happy. I mean it's better than
You know what it is? You know what it is about me? You know what it is about me?
It's not the six inches. It's the way that I fucking just love to fucking perform on a woman.
I just love it. I like to fucking go. I like to go, go, and go.
Yeah, you know. It takes me a whole. It takes me a very long time to come.
It takes me a very long time to come, crazy Dino.
I mean, as long as you know how to fight, then that's all that matters.
As long as you know how to fight, because if a dude is just like,
you know how to fuck good and he's lasting for a whole hour,
that shit would be just annoying, like on some real shit, like no.
But you know, but you know, on some, on some real shit, on some real shit, vaginas are very sensitive and I like to fucking hurt them. I like to hurt them.
Ah.
Wow.
Wow, thank you.
Know this guy this guy's pretty cool. I like this guy a lot. Someone said what they say they say that
Hey, bro, not everybody's gonna be a fan of me not everybody's gonna like me but everybody will fucking learn who the fuck I am though
Okay, sure. Yeah
Cool, we're all smoking our
I'm not
Didn't just come out of the blue trust me
Sike yes
So, what do you what do you?
So what is what's your choice of poison? I know you like to smoke weed because I just saw you smoking weed
But yeah, you drink beer. Yeah, I drink I've been drinking a lot less lately
But yeah, I drink like twisted teas and hard lemonade and
You know sometimes a little bit harder alcohol, but I've been just smoking recently and
That's pretty much it right now. I've done every every drug in the past, but you know, I'm just good to
Sick, it's just like the milder shit
So so nowadays you just just like to smoke your weed. It's not what you're saying. Oh, yeah
No, someone said like in the chat the chat someone said you'd like cocaina you'd like that or no, okay?
Okay, you know that shit that shit can definitely be fun
It's an expensive habit, but that's fine
Let me let me teach you something auto so you said you got a six-inch or so what you got to do is what you didn't tell the chat
Or the panel is you got to spread them butt cheeks. You're going a little deeper. You know what I mean?
Just like with both hands just spread the butt cheeks when you're
When you're behind, you know
That's a technique
I mean, I mean, that's that's
I appreciate your input.
random guys. Oh, it's like
way deeper. Way deeper.
I cannot talk about some
I'm sorry
I cannot I can't talk about it, okay, okay, I understand I won't do that again. I'm sorry. I got you
I just wanted to say this input
No, no, I heard you say cocaine, but I you know what I mean. I'm not gonna get into it
Okay, okay, no problem. I'm sorry. I apologize. This is someone in the chat said something about that
But I mean, I don't mind cocaine that but it's like it's not very strong for me
It's it's kind of a
Kind of we didn't do anything, but he doesn't want to talk about it
He didn't have a problem with random guys. Oh, I don't know
I thought you said you didn't want to talk about it in front of him. So I understand you can come back up
I have no problem with a random guy, bro. I don't know who random
Okay
What I meant to say, there's some things I won't be able to talk about
That's it. I got you. I got you. Yeah
Bro, I'm confident. I don't give a fuck. I'll tell you
Okay, it's just because I know it's just because I know there's a thousand people that know me, okay?
Yeah, yeah, you're well, you're well known on YouTube, right? Yeah, you're kind of
Oh, yeah, I'm well known. I'm well known and don't worry about it. I'm not gonna fucking. Okay
Come on, bro
Okay, cool. Yeah. Yeah, I'm well known, bro
And here's in here on this goddamn fucking internet bitch and in real life both
I'm well known. So I have to be careful. It's okay. It's okay. Yeah, okay. That's good. Yeah. Yes
Looking at their crazy smile
What happened?
What were you thinking about?
I'm just high right now. Like I'm just high as fuck
Like
I'm just zoning out just hi
and yeah
What about you which what's on your mind?
Yeah, you can't be that high you just fucking vaping you just vaping up the shit over here is strong
Minnesota weed is pretty strong actually like this is from the disco what one
28 30% not even I don't have the package but
It's pretty strong. I mean
It's up there like with Cali weed and shit. So that's just pretty good
I'm in Canada, I'm in Canada. So you do know you do know
weed is nuts around you. Yeah, we did over there, too. Um,
I've had weed from Denver and that show is pretty good
Denver yeah Denver weed is really good
Or like Colorado, I guess got fucking we chop they got we chop
Yeah, they got
That hello wheat shops in Colorado Colorado weed is bomb as fuck like
That show was fucking fire
That's also pretty cool
Did you did you visit a wheat shop in Minnesota because that's what you are right now
Already got weed from the shops everywhere
Yeah, it's good here the weeds good here
But I don't know like I mean
There's not as much options as I can Cali like in Cali like there's so many different shops and such over here
They don't have any recreational shops
But they do have it like if you got the license and shit
So that's what the difference is like I'm used to like going to these shops or whenever I wanted and over here
It's not as easy
So yeah
Very I don't know if you heard about London. I'm telling you. I don't know if you learn
I don't know if you heard about London on your Canada, but this we chops in every corner now
And it's the best fucking weed ever, but I don't smoke weed
I smoke it here and there who I am. I'm a fucking alcoholic. I like the likes pussy
That's who I am. I'm a alcoholic
Yeah, yeah, every now and then bro. Every now and then bro. I'll fucking go to a week shop and buy me a couple talks
nice
Like right now
Hey, you're crazy demon right now if I want to there's a week shot
I think five ten minutes I can walk to a week right now five five five minute walk
I can walk to a week shop right now and buy the weed that I want and whatever but I don't do that
I'd rather go to a beer store and buy more beer. I
Rather go to a beer store and buy more beer because that's that's I like my beer
You know, I like my beer. I drink beer I chill with it
Drink it
I mean, yeah, I drink also. I mean, I mainly smoke, but I do drink
Sorry one second. I'm just getting something right now
No, it's all good. It's all good. I don't understand why I'm here by myself
Hello camera. Oh sake always leaves
He's um, he's wearing push tacos right now
What the fuck are you fixing up?
What the fuck are you fixing up, psyche?
Look at this, look at this.
I don't call him psyche.
I call him psyche.
Did you see that?
It says anal.
I don't know.
It says anal right there.
Anal? What?
It says anal.
I don't know why. It's kind of weird.
Okay, here we go.
Oh, yeah, okay. Oh, I can use my chat from this this the tablet now. So that's good. Okay. Hi guys
I'm in the chat now. I just had to
Wow, so
What else guys? Um
How how was your weekend? Did you have a nice weekend?
Give me a weekend. Oh, yeah, both of you
You have a nice weekend
Hey, it's I'm always lit. I'm always lit always. It's okay
That's the way I answer
That's the way I answer you. I'm with it. So I
Mean comic comic auto, but uh, yeah
Those no no I'm fire fire
I'm fire fire. I'm always lit all day every day. There's nothing you can do about it. I'm okay with it
Yeah, work tomorrow. Do you work tomorrow?
Like I said, like I said fight there's some things I can not
Understand that bro
You understand that bro. There's a ton of fucking people waiting for me to say the wrong thing. I
Got you. I hear you. It's YouTube. So yeah, if you get a little bit careful, yeah
Yeah, oh
Yeah, yeah, sorry, let me ask you something right now
Okay, let me ask you something right now. Okay, right, right
Some fucking dude, right? And if I see you, well, I subscribe to you. I subscribe to you and shit like that
What is this members only? What is this members only?
the members only is
The members are able to
To see all the past episodes are on just like private for members only all the old episodes
But we have summer here too. Hey, so that has to have a summer
Hey, what's up with auto and diamond or demon?
But you didn't finish what you were saying, bro. Oh
To the dude
Auto, yeah
Hey, what's up some
Hey, so I heard you were saying my name earlier
Excuse me. Yes, of course. You're a beautiful woman. Yes, and
Yes, thank you for that part. But what was the bitches thing? You think we're all
Excuse me. Excuse me. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Hey, come on. Let's let's not start this way
Hey, let's not start this way. I'm a man. Okay
You're a bad man. What?
Oh, I know I don't have a dick so you ain't got nothing to say is that what it is
Let's fuck truck. Let's fuck truck. I'm a man. Yeah, you came a-running didn't you fucking weirdo?
Hey
Man you gotta get on the fucking internet and call women bitches. You ain't no fucking man short-ass little boy
Shut the fuck up. What does having to be a man had to do anything?
She's a pussy like that's why I started laughing to be honest with you like when he said I'm a man like what?
I'm not fucking good. We ain't even hearing you. Okay. You ain't you ain't you ain't tall enough to have a deep way
So over talk me short fuck. So shut up
Hey, I'm a man if you want to start I'm a man
Don't give a fuck between the last make sure your balls are still there because you clearly ain't had them in the last 45 minutes pussy
Summer are you a bitch? I don't give a fuck. I don't give a yeah. I'm a bitch. I'm a bitch
I sure a fuck yeah, and you called me a bitch. So I came up here to be a bitch
All right, so what the fuck do you get offended?
What I did not I got tired when you talk about I got tired of your fucking conversation
So I came up here to fuck with you since you called us all bitches early
All right, let's say they say fucking finish what what my wish I got right with me talk
So you shut the fuck up
Yeah. You don't tell nobody what to do. You don't tell nobody what to do.
What the fuck you think? You ain't tall enough to ride this ride, motherfucker. Shut up.
I don't say so so
And then you come live and then we can just come up on the fucking panel right I don't have to be like members only
You're balls ain't drum-boggin' up, boy. You're fuckin' way too soft.
You'll make a difference.
I got a deeper voice than you got, Pussy.
Shut up! No one gives a fuck what you're talkin' about, dude.
I got a bigger dick than you do. How about that?
Summer. Summer. You'll make a difference.
I'm still in line to celebrate. You got six inches.
You got six inches?
Boy, you ain't even six inches. What the fuck you talkin' about? You got six inches.
You're not even six inches. Shut the fuck up.
Actually, thank you very much because that gives me even more of a
Because I'm actually
City I've seen you stare in the diamond cities get them girl get that money from
Summer!
Hey, it was definitely a little bit of a pity!
Is this the same is this the same samas yesterday say yeah that you were thirsty being thirsty over
Yeah, sure the fuck is the one you was drooling over motherfucker. It sure is don't call me a bitch again
You call me a bitch and but also try to say I'm sexy
You're gonna get the right side of me and it ain't the side that you're tall enough for motherfucker. How about that?
Do you know what the thing is? You know what a thing?
You're another incel
You're another trainee chaser on fucking line. That's what you are. That's what diamond just exposed you
Because your show was looking at her titties. You ought to try you want to give her some money as much as you was staring at her titties
Summer summer
No one cares. I don't know. I don't care. No one cares. No one cares
We're gonna call you a bitch. How much you had to drink? How many lines I've got? I'm a bitch. Call me a bitch
I don't care. I'm a bitch, baby. What a capital B honey
I love it! I understand that. I'm the bitch. I'm the, I'm the bitch.
I didn't call you a bitch though, bro. I just got here, bro.
I just got here, bro.
I just got here.
I'm not a bro. I don't have a dick.
I'm not a bro. Don't call me a fucking bro, you weirdo.
Alright, bitch.
that's right address me the right way mother short motherfucker bitch all right
all right good all right bitch all right and give that it make sure you give
diamond and tip the way you were looking at her titties you weird motherfucker
and we all watched you you was drooling over them titties you was
drooling over them titties you know who the fuck you talking to summer I'm give
a fuck who I'm talking to because you ain't tall enough
Again to ride this ride for fuck
You thank you somebody on I guess somewhere else in another computing bed over here bitches don't give a fuck about in cells and you're an insult
So I don't give a fuck
Fuck in my in cell. I just got here
Look at you motherfucker. You weren't sitting here. It takes two but two minutes to find out you were fucking you're an incel dude
I'm fucking laying my ass.
How's that bald spot on the top of your head going?
I'll pick you up, Mark, and make you fucking question
all your manhood the name of the fucker you play with me.
How's that fucking receiving an airline on your fucking head?
Hey, bend over so I can fix my makeup on that bald spot
on the top of your head.
I need to fix my eyeliner.
I need a mirror, bitch.
It's gonna take you a whole lot longer to fucking
You think I'm mute to us?
Yeah, dumb dumb as my friend goes would say.
You're both fucking dumb dumb dumb dumb.
Oh, you're little dumb dumb, because ain't nothing big about you.
Not even your personality.
You can't even talk over me.
You can't even control this situation,
but you're going to call yourself a man.
You can't even control this fucking conversation.
I'm gonna keep talking.
No one cares, dude.
No one cares.
Bring your mask.
Bend over so I can see that bald spot.
No, let me see that bald spot.
You know you want to go chase that hairline and you'll be losing mother fucker because I'm a god
Spray your neck, let's have a conversation
You want to go that way?
You want to go that way, dumb?
Spray your neck mother fucker, it's been leaving you for a while
Shut the fuck up
Shut up dude
You're six hundred painters, you can't do nothing with that pussy
I guarantee you I'll make you come big.
I'll make you come big.
Yeah, I'll make a bitch come any fucking everybody you can't carry without telling everybody you do cocaine. I can't talk about
I know what you're looking at. I know what you're looking at. You're looking at a man, but you know what I'm a liar
Okay, I can't tell you a new cocaine get somebody might clip it and send it to my boss
She was
I'm a tiger, I'm a tiger, I'm a tiger, I'm a tiger, I'm a tiger, I'm a tiger, I'm a tiger, I'm a tiger, I'm a tiger, I'm a tiger, I'm a tiger, I'm a tiger, I'm a tiger, I'm a tiger, I'm a tiger, I'm a tiger, I'm a tiger, I'm a tiger, I'm a tiger, I'm a tiger, I'm a tiger, I'm a tiger, I'm a tiger, I'm a tiger, I'm a tiger, I'm a tiger, I'm a tiger, I'm a tiger, I'm a tiger, I'm a tiger, I'm a tiger, I'm a tiger, I'm a tiger, I'm a tiger, I'm a tiger, I'm a tiger, I'm a tiger, I'm a tiger, I'm a tiger, I'm a tiger, I'm a tiger, I'm a tiger, I'm a tiger, I'm a tiger, I'm a
What the fuck would it be Andy, bro? Just get the vines. Get the vines.
I'm angry. I'm having fun with your stupid ass.
No, you having fun? I just can't do it.
I am, actually.
You having fun?
Okay.
Yeah.
The night's too young. Don't worry.
I bet you I do. I bet I can make before the cry before the end of the night's over with.
Oh, yeah
Don't ever call me a bitch again when you don't know me that's your fucking problem. You want to call me a bitch
I'm gonna treat you like the bitch you are
Dude, stop with your face. You don't look tough
You look like a fucking reject harder than I get no hugs in the ever in his life. So shut up
I never called you anything. Yeah, I called you. I don't care. No one gives a fuck. No one gives a fuck
I called you a beautiful flower, if you're in a bad mood, that's not my shit, that's not my shit.
I'm not in a bad mood at all. I'm in a great mood.
Oh, are you? Are you? And that's why you want to, and that's why you want to fucking come here and fucking do this bullshit?
Shut the fuck up.
I'm not having a good time. That's what I do every day.
I got time too. I got time too. I got all kinds of time. I got all kinds of time.
Don't ever fucking confuse me don't ever confuse me. Oh
You're so tough
You're so tough. Hey honey, honey. I never told you
Honey, I never called you a bitch, honey. What the fuck you hallucinating you are
give me a favor bend over and let me see the top of your head so I can fix my
ladder I see at my fucking mirror up there don't me a favor don't me a favor
and please better fucking know who the fuck you talk to fuck you ain't tall
enough to ride this ride I told you what boy
You think somebody's intimidated about motherfuckers is five foot. I'm five foot you four eleven motherfucker. You think I'm scared of you
Shut up
Hey, don't know a man trying to ever intimidate a woman a pussy does
Until you come right there around one. They don't give a fuck about none of that ain't nobody scared of you
You know what happens to most men when when a women goes wild, you know what happens to me look like I don't really care
You know what happens to most men? I don't really give us it
They'd be pussy. You know what happens to me? I get a hard
And we can all tell we can tell when you had you had a hard day when you were talking to diamond
You know like Barry
another one bites the desk.
Hey, David, thanks for getting
out of the way for us, girl.
At least we know who they are.
Oh, my God, it sucks.
Six inches break.
Come on.
Girl.
Both of your wolves.
I promise you.
No disrespect at all.
Because six inches is coming in an hour
Can you feel it between your walls it's
Okay, your voice is it ain't even big enough to talk over like we don't hear anything you're saying nor do we give a fuck pussy
That's what you failed to realize
You want to internet and you definitely look definitely I'm glad you told the truth about buying pussy because you definitely buy pussy baby
Sama, you know what you're gonna do, Sama, you're gonna take a screenshot and you're gonna fucking masturbate to me
That's what you're gonna do
You're receiving heroin? Are you kidding me dude? You have fucking more glaze in your beer than fucking, come on dude get the fuck outta here
If I was going to masturbate on anybody, a bitch on anybody I want, it ain't gonna be you homie.
I can promise you that.
Okay.
Oh, that's another fucking short film.
Bitches.
Fuck, I look like masturbating here.
And I'm going to masturbate on something and it's gonna be a sick, sick, sick.
It ain't a little thing. It's an average
but still women if you want to dream a
set you don't dream of something it's bigger
right?
Or bigger titties. That's smaller titties.
Or a bigger ass.
This is the way you want it.
You don't want someone having a conversation with you.
Not you. No, I don't.
This is the way you're going to fucking have it.
This is the way you're going to fucking have fire fire.
I'm scared.
I scarred psyche.
I scarred.
I just don't know what to do if I say I'm psychic.
Oh, look at the girl. I'm scared.
Let's go.
Come get me.
Oh, God.
Put your pussy out.
Put your pussy out. Let me see it.
What?
Shut the fuck up.
Let me see that pussy.
You ain't got enough money. You fucking reject her.
Huh?
You could have been to Mother Blaine because you couldn't do it, boo boo.
Okay.
Hey, boo boo. Hey, boo boo.
I'll be back. I gotta go back
to work. I'm like this.
I'll be back. I'll show you my
six inches. Show me. She left.
She left. She left. She had to
go back to work. Hey, you're
psych. Hey, you're psych. I'm
trying to connect with this
That's the way she wants. That's the way she wants. Okay. I'm gonna connect with her. Okay. Okay. What?
Okay, well, I don't think that's like very productive. Hold on Bosworth
Yo, what's up? Oh, easy one second. Easy
I don't know
This is auto and then diamonds on the on the phone to you
Well, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh,
uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh,
She wants me to control her and I'm going to control her. Just
control her. How are you going to control her? How are you
just talking? What are you just talking and flirty? What are
you talking about? I'm going to put a leash on that bitch. How
are you going to control it? I'll come back later. I'll come
Make it easy. Yeah, it's a little crazy on that bitch
Can I recommend you get something first
Shit bro, who the fuck you think you're talking to bro auto
Nothing
I don't want to shut the fuck up. I don't want to shut the fuck up. I don't want to shut the fuck up. I don't want to shut the fuck up. I don't want to shut the fuck up. I don't want to shut the fuck up. I don't want to shut the fuck up. I don't want to shut the fuck up. I don't want to shut the fuck up. I don't want to shut the fuck up. I don't want to shut the fuck up. I don't want to shut the fuck up. I don't want to shut the fuck up. I don't want to shut the fuck up. I don't want to shut the fuck up. I don't want to shut the fuck up. I don't want to shut the fuck up. I don't want to shut the fuck up. I don't want to shut the fuck up. I don't want to shut the fuck up. I don't want to shut the fuck up. I don't want to shut the fuck up. I don't
I
Slap your real quick I slap your real quick stupid damn bitch. Nice to meet you. Nice to meet you, but that gangsta shit
Hey, you know what summer summer summer if you wanna if you wanna summer if you wanna summer
I'll give you a summer. I'll give you a summer. What?
Yeah summer season right now. I don't get it
Well, I'll give her off fucking summer
So low to the back guy
I do inside
Appreciate it
No problem, how are you doing today?
JC's pussy is wet you need to go over there and dry it for but he was just talking to flirty
Why are you up here bothering these people auto you dumb fucker?
If you'd like to just smash that motherfucker right in the face go ahead, bro. I'm welcome here
sake
So, so what was up, why are you going?
I'm on A-bitch, that's it bro.
You're not answering my question.
Didn't you
Remember the other night when you left JC all crying and everything cuz you thought JC didn't love you
Did you get over that auto there?
Is it love?
Yeah, that's what you're talking about, bro.
You got all of what are you talking about, bro?
What are you talking about, bro?
Great question.
Again, can I ask you a question?
So, Otto, you want to fuck Flirty?
Let's just get out the way you want to fuck flirty that's what he does. Yeah, my name's Billy
I think crazy demon has a beautiful smile. Yes, of course. She has a beautiful you want to fuck flirty diamond
That means I don't want to fuck her. No, I don't want to fuck her. I
Like
Look look what I'm doing right now
I'm taking a piss because I can't why are you going pee in front of us?
Why we
We're those some of your friends are in my chat
I don't I'm gonna check my list
Okay
Between taking a fucking piece in the corner
Taking a piece. I don't look like you're literally looking at us. Why you go
This way you go pee because do you have a
Do you have a weird why would you be staring at us? Why you go pee though?
If I need to take a piece I'm gonna take a piece you have a home auto you have a home. Yeah
Yeah
Is it a tent?
No, it's not a tent
It's only homeless people only homeless people do stupid shit like that piss on stream in front of
You think that you're outlawed by taking a piss out in the streets like a homeless person that's crazy work
Let me get psych. You got some fucking links. You got some fucking links coming around here, huh?
What you gonna get from me I ain't no fucking name
You're lame. I ain't no you're lame. What the fuck is gonna be lame summer? You want to be a bitch?
I'm gonna fucking get you a leak on bird asshole. I'm gonna get you a leech
Get it right asshole you speaking of bronze bird asshole
Are we done? No. Are we done?
We're not done. We're not done.
Okay. Okay. So, what? So, what?
We're not done. So, what?
We're not done. This is I don't
like looking at your lips. I
don't like looking at your
I don't like looking at your
Is
Let me recommend something for you bro
So you can care that ball spot you
Nothing you can do about it as soon as i'm not fucking around
As long as I don't show you, you black garbage bags to the nearest place, I don't want you showing your dick to me.
I don't want to see your fucking dick.
I don't want to see your dick.
No, you're fine.
You're fine, you're fine, you're fine.
I don't want to see your dick.
Am I allowed to defend myself?
Yes.
Say my name pussy. Say my name pussy. Say my name. You need to put that on a leash motherfucker. You need to go find your receiving hairline. That's the only thing you need to concentrate on it. Shut the fuck up pussy. You fucking weirdo. All right.
What the fuck was that bro? You say a few words and you holla what the fuck?
I'm not that hard. I know what you're saying. You was about to take a piss with me.
Yeah, yeah, but why the fuck would you go and holla and fucking dick and fucking hey
You fucking flew out of here faster than a
sixty hundred thousand dollar car
Bitch, you'll never have in your life
Take public transportation just like me asshole. What do you mean?
You ain't got no car. You ain't got no car. You ain't got no car. You ain't got no car, you ain't got no car, you ain't got no car, you ain't got no car, you ain't got no car, you ain't got no car, you ain't got no car, you ain't got no car, you ain't got no car, you ain't got no car, you ain't got no car, you ain't got no car, you ain't got no car, you ain't got no car, you ain't got no car, you ain't got no car, you ain't got no car, you ain't got no car, you ain't got no car, you ain't got no car, you ain't got no car, you ain't got no car, you ain't got no car, you ain't got no car, you ain't got no car, you ain't got no car, you ain't got no car, you ain't got no car, you ain't got no car
I don't need to be I told you I got I just got down telling you I love flower you ain't got no
You ain't got no car, you got a shopping cart, you ain't got no car, you ain't got no car, you ain't got no car, you got a shopping cart, you got a shopping cart, you got a shopping cart, you ain't got no car, you got a shopping cart, you got a shopping cart, you got a shopping cart, you got a shopping cart, you got a shopping cart, you ain't got no car, you got a shopping cart, you ain't got no car, you got a shopping cart, you ain't got no car, you got a shopping cart, you ain't got no car, you got a shopping cart, you ain't got no car, you got a shopping cart, you ain't got no car, you got a shopping cart, you ain't got no car, you got a shopping cart, you ain't got no car, you got a shopping cart, you ain't got no car, you got a shopping cart, you ain't got no car, you got a shopping cart, you ain't got
Get her off her pussy. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. You ain't gonna do shit. You ain't gonna do shit.
You're just up here talking. Say my name. Say my name. Say my name, pussy.
I'm gonna go to a farmer.
Look, you got a woman to wind him up. Now watch him go.
Collar! Collar!
You need a real man. You need a real man to reach you.
And you found one. You found a real man.
You found a real man?
You need a six inches.
You a real man. You a man with chat lips. You know what I'm saying?
Because you ain't got no
No car
Yeah, if I want to save some money
Or would I go to Walmart?
Want to say some money go to Walmart, right?
And get a fucking rich for this bitch
No, no, you so you can put your bottles in there, you know what I mean and those dirty clothes you got from like a
Come on bro. I'm not for a woman bro. Get me a fucking cheeck, fucking leash. Bro, you ain't gonna do nothing though. You don't have fucking six inches. Like six inches is nothing.
I'm a fucking get a leech. You don't have a leech bro. You two broke. You want to be a bitch? I'ma get you a leech. I'ma be a bitch.
You can't do shit with your six inch hairs. I'm even on my bird. I'ma be a bitch. What now? You wanna be a bitch? I'ma get you a nice
You can, you can, you can leash me if you try.
I like to give you one.
You know what?
I thought leech is going to have a butterfly.
I can, I can buy your whole life for 50 cents a day.
I can donate to your life.
I'm going to get you some breakfast in the morning.
You can't have breakfast.
You can't have breakfast because that's what you want.
I'm the mental handle a bitch
You in a rehab program? You in a rehab program?
You're only five fucking feet
You're five foot with six inches
Like you aren't ever gonna do shit
You are never going to be five foot one. You have six inches.
How the fuck am I five foot one? And I'm strong as a whole.
You're literally only five foot. You're not five foot one.
How the fuck am I five foot one?
You just said you were five foot, like, not even 30 minutes ago.
You said you were five foot. Now you're five foot one.
When he said his height is, he said he's five foot one.
He said he was five foot. Now he's claiming to be five foot one.
Dude, you said you were five foot.
How the fuck, how the fuck am I fight food one and be a
You are only five fun you have fucking six inches like you want to see you can't see nothing
I'm fight food one and I'm
At least those six inches like that is pathetic
My dick is six inches I don't like
I don't like
But how am I, how am I
That's six inches
How am I strong?
How am I supposed to, how am I supposed to, how am I supposed to, how am I supposed to
foot one?
You're supposed to foot one.
You literally said you were five foot, you didn't say you were five foot one.
Stop line it by your age stop line it by your height. I mean
I'm five foot one six inches
But how am I five foot one?
I'm big.
How am I as big as you?
How did that happen?
How did I get so big as you?
Some bitch
You ready for that auto you ready for that auto
You thoughtful one, right? So the thing about
I'm also a size 11 so I can put these size 11 sneakers
When I'm on the panel
You're not even taller than
Think about it. Does your feet touch the floor?
You know what? You know what? I tried nice. I tried nice with Samma. I told her she's a nice
Why do you say her name like that?
I
Try to tell her she's a nice-looking woman and this is what
She likes it
No woman likes being caught a bitch by a man that's five foot only has six inches
That's what she met. She met the man that's gonna fucking buy a leash from Walmart. And I'm a leash stop bitch. You're broke. You get no need for Walmart. Like you're broken. You're broke. Real quick. Real quick. Real quick. Why would I spend so much money on a leash? Because you don't have it. You don't have it. You don't have it. Where's all your bestos? Where's all your bestos?
No, that's not it. I cannot do that.
All right, I'm not gonna fucking bitch
No, bro. I'm gonna go to Walmart and buy the cheapest fucking leech and I'm a leech
You're not even gonna buy it you're probably gonna steal it with your bro
Why you can't buy an expensive one from Walmart?
Why you gotta buy a cheap one my bro guys my bro cause you don't know me bro
You don't know nothing about me
You know me. You know me. You know about me. You know about me. You don't know shit about me
I know you got crack lips and you smoke cigarettes and you need to be in an AA
And you're too short to go on the fucking ride
I know that your feet don't touch the floor when you sit in the chair. So I mean pretty much
I know a couple of things about you Otto
Uh-huh, and it's crazy
Hair club for men you need that so of course
So of course someone's gonna call you auto like you don't people that don't have that name on here auto don't got no auto
Let me let me let me let me make some things clear
You can call me fire fire
Don't fucking call me out. If you don't fucking know me. What up auto? What up auto?
Yeah
You speak it to a man, man.
Fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, bro.
I'm talking to Otto, no.
Fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, me, bro.
Yeah, I'm talking to you.
Yeah, I mean, yes, I'm like you.
Yes, you take a blame like you, I will never be like you.
You are never you can't afford Walmart.
You spit every single time you talk.
Yeah, and and I'll come out your mouth every time you talk
because you got chat with and and and and are you my wife?
Are you my wife?
I'm your father.
I'm your father Otto. My father. My father. You wouldn't know. You wouldn't know what
the fuck a father is. Oh really? Why do you say that? I know my father. Why do I say that?
Because I am your father.
Got a father around this bitch and you're gonna fucking like you. How do you figure you're gonna?
Oh, yeah, Walmart. Oh, yeah, Walmart. Well, I'm not a woman
What are you down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down down
I can fuck a bitch if I want to be a homeless this is that one day that's not a problem.
Did you forget who the fuck I got in my contacts if I want to watch all the homeless people
that stay around you that got tense for you and and you met them from a shelter that's
Did you forget two weeks ago? I pounded a bitch. I banged the shit out of her. She came
Okay, so you fuck you fuck the bitch in a tent
Were you fucking for crack
And that's true story
I don't know why you bragging about fucking another homeless bitch
It's really crazy, bro. Like you're that you don't get kudo point
Why are you jealous?
Do I even know you
Why am I even talking to you bro because I'm trying to help you rightfully deserve
Of course I don't know you, of course you don't know me, but I don't know you, but you know me, how does that work, how does that work, how does that work, how does that work for you, is that how it goes in your real life?
You don't know anybody, you don't know anybody bro in your real life.
I see guys like you every day on the streets with a cardboard box sign and what happens is they're like
I'll suck your dick for beer. I've seen you with that
I need I need a wild lot. I need a beer sign
You know, I need money for crack. I need money for drugs. I see you you pair handle
I just see you pair handle on e-train you homeless, bro
I don't even understand how you get cell phone reception as broke as you are, bro. It's bad
Hey
You know why your words sound to me they sound like music, so I'm just gonna fucking dance. I like it
Yes, dance to my fucking voice, bitch
I just discovered a new move fuck you bitch
What
I just discovered a new move, a new dancing move.
Who are you, blue?
Yeah, can you dance for me?
So how does that dance move go?
Do you shimmy?
I'll dance for you.
Here it goes.
Dance for us.
Can you dance your snake for us?
I'm dancing.
That's a seizure.
What?
I'm dancing. You want me to dance? I'll dance. Look. Look at me dance. No, you got to put
your phone down so we can see you dance. Shut up, bitch. Yo, you know, you just danced
The hairs on your head whatever's left. Just started waiting. So I just saw that. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, okay. Okay, bro
Okay, bro. Talk to me like you know me. Yes. Yes, bro. She I just gave you change
You know me, okay, talk to me like you know me. Okay. I know you are. I gave you change of the day, bro
Shut the fuck up. You have some appreciation. No me from
People on the street
No, okay psych psych
Yeah, psych
Yeah
I'm here. I am the new father. I am the new father
You understand me
You're the new father, okay, okay, what father what?
I am the new I am the new father
What that's it?
Little kids these little kids are fucking crying and throwing 10
You are throw a tantrum bro
bro
Bro, bro. I am new. I am your new father and you can never be my father. You homeless
You're gonna love me
You're gonna love this money you gonna love these new shoes I give you
You're gonna love this new shelter I got for you, bro, you're gonna love this new shelter homie
You're gonna love this new shopping cart I'm gonna get from you from Walmart
You're gonna fucking see
The face of the new father father of homelessness. I see you guys every day. You ain't
You can call me father garbage can you can call me whatever but you're gonna be
You're gonna fucking be well, and you're gonna be okay about do you have any other dance moves?
Yeah, I have I have other dance moves. Hey, I'm just hey, let me let me just
Look listen. I
Am the new father around here. So yeah, I showed you how to dance move
Take it easy. Yeah, we got the other dance moves
What you know what if you want to save me a trip to Walmart, do you have a leech just hanging around?
now well because I mean send it to me because I got a bitch and this bitch
needs to be leached right now hey no no no no no you want to be fucking leached
stupid bitch I'll leach you
You've been ranting about this shit for like 30 minutes
All right, 30 minutes. All right, 30 minutes. Guess what 30 minutes. Guess what?
Half an hour. That's it half an hour. And this is me
I'm gonna let you all go and I'm gonna let you all fucking think about me mother fucker
Oh
కికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికిక
No, this guy's cool. He's cool. This guy's a cool guy guys. He's a cool guy. He's a nice, cool guy.
No one's being mean.
I hate to break it to you. He is a lame piece of shit.
I don't know why we post that in the fuckery of a homeless man.
I already asked him to like show us how to dance move for us. That's all.
He was dancing for us.
Did you see what happened? What'd you tell me? I didn't give orders to psych. Did you see that?
You don't give orders not your panel when you get a job and you get your money else
You can get you can get something called
You can't do that. You can't do that on a certain day and give your mother a shit.
Broke ass. Maybe you can turn on those fucking potatoes.
You need a crying puppy. You need a crying puppy.
You need a crying puppy to piss you all over around, eh?
Fuck around, eh? Fuck around.
Well, goddamn job saying get a job, but you're broke ass.
Don't talk to me. You don't know me, bro.
Maybe then, if you get set up, they have a stream, you know,
where you think the world's in, and you can have a stream.
I don't want to kill.
I'm here to make sure.
Kill.
I'm here to make psych famous. I'm not here to make
all of you fucking famous.
Nobody knows you. Who the fuck you gonna make famous?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Don't talk don't talk. You have a small dick. You can't cook that shit because you cook out of a can in a hot pan.
Your dick is fucking small and you're fucking homeless and you can't shower. You start your dinner with a fucking lighter which you broke at.
You stink
You smell like fucking donkey ass
You smell like straight up donkey ass
And you fucking have a small dick
You have a small fucking dick
And it's perfect
You
You don't know me stupid freehold it rice. Yeah, I'm getting no rice and like put on some fucking chapstick and like
You have crunchy rice
From Honduras
I'm from Honduras. He ain't
You don't know me.
You're in America now. You're in
America. Yeah. Well, this is
Let this motherfucker go.
You don't know me. Stupid.
You have a small dick. I know that you have a small dick.
Jim, are you there Jim?
Yes, yes I am, yes.
Okay, who are you Jim? Do you want to talk to Otto too?
Just relax mate, I'm not going to poem or anything.
Okay.
I've been on here before.
Hi, how are you?
You have a small fucking dick, Otto, and you're fucking short as fuck, and it's sad.
Yeah, and?
You can't even force it from Walmart.
Well, that's the cheapest fucking wish I can get for summer.
You're broke
I'm on a budget
Bitch
Hey, bronze bird, do you want to hear about what someone else's stream?
You want to fucking talk?
You want to talk to Otto, you want to talk to Firefire?
I think you'll be on the stream.
I think that's a big mistake to fuck around.
It's a big mistake to fuck around with Firefire.
It's like black and bruised because of it.
He likes to punch his own penis and slap it and abuse it and shit.
That's what he'd done on somebody else's stream, because he was off his face.
What's he doing?
Wait, wait.
When we talking about this guy, it's like all those doing that shit?
Yeah, yeah, he'd done it on somebody else. I'll not say who his streamer was,
but he got very excited at females being on the stream that he found attractive,
and he was very, very drunk. It was late in the day,
and he'd had too much of the Peruvian marching powder, too much of the yeyo.
And his eyes was rolling in his head, and he started punching it and slapping it.
Oh, so Otto is an end self for real?
He likes to hurt himself down there, and he's got, he had bruises on it.
Ew.
This is not crazy.
Otto, did you punch your own dick?
Play
How much crazy can come out of people a how much crazy why do you punch your fucking dick?
When I get home I'm wasted and I want my dick up so I punch it so he wakes up
Because it's dead instead after all the alcohol in the EU
So I punch it so he wakes up. Yeah
So you have a cook dick you don't get hard cuz you have a coke dick
No, no, I got this day. You mentioned early that you do cocaine. Ah, you said that you do little sniff here and there
When the fuck did I say cocaine stupid earlier?
You're like you've literally said that you did cocaine
Hey, bro. Hey, bro
I want to tell you right now right here right now when my dick doesn't wake up. I'll punch it
I'll punch it
I will punch my dick and I'll punch my balls. So my dick wakes up
You like doing it for the people you're a bit of an exhibitionist and the masochist aren't you out of it?
Yeah, yeah, and yeah, and because I want my dick to wake up. What else do you like?
What other freaky stuff do you like?
shut up a crazy demon shut up you like you like your date being punched what
else you like it probably likes like cooking electric
only my second day only my second day come on relax
You're you're a disgusting little golem. Shut the fuck up, bro. I get
And when I get home and I don't see pussy at home and my dick doesn't wake up
I'll punch it. I'll punch it until he wakes up
I wonder whether people do the same to you. Oh when you're sleeping
So like anybody can punch your dick and it'll get hard
Yeah, yeah, why not?
I like it, I like it
It's bruised like
Diamond it's bruised it had bruises on it
But it doesn't have bruises bro. It's just fucking
Big bro, sometimes I just gonna wake it up and if it takes a slump
I'll slap, I'll slap my dick around like nothing.
What?
It's bruised.
It was black and blue.
I don't care, bro.
I'll slap my own dick.
It's on your dick.
Bro.
I'll, bro.
I'll slap my balls and my dick until he wakes up.
So what?
Oh.
Hey, Otto, can we, can we knock off the fucking gutter talk for a minute?
Fucking it's shut it shut the fuck up for a second
Fucking big mouth for a minute
Because God he invited me
What the fuck up hey, why did you mute yourself I come up here to talk to you
Mad Jim don't fuck around
Don't fuck around Billy
You're the dumbest parker here you sitting here insulting this woman you don't even know her
You're lucky you're not on my panel cuz I first time you call her
You be gone I'd kick it from my panel
You're an idiot
Go back to Jaycee's where you belong. Same with you mad Jim because you used to hide underneath rusty
And now you're over Jaycee's you want to control me Jim mad Jim you come up here. Oh, I'm not gonna burn bum you
So he's in with rum and vanguard and the rest of them and that's what they do. They're porn bombers
Yes, you are yes, you are yes, you are yes, you are
Well, and you support the former you're not friends with rum is back in vanguard you're gonna deny that
Have I done it?
No, I haven't you see you won't answer the question yet
How do I know my dad in with them you laugh right along with them and everything. Yeah, you did it
No Roman I fell out. Yeah. Yeah, you did. No. Yeah, you did. Yeah, you did
Birdie demon, that's I love that name. That's a great name. Thank you
Shut your fucking mouth auto and go fucking play god damn you well no
They're fucking tar and feather and you go ahead make yourself look like a dick in front of a lot of people you don't even know bye
I'm in them. Mr. Hayden was the sailor so he doesn't mind him.
Otto, where you at?
Oh his phone keeps freezing.
You're frozen.
The users of the people's Wi-Fi you see that's how he stands out in the street and drinks
warm beers and steals Wi-Fi from free Wi-Fi spots.
And then when somebody comes up when there's too many people on the camera on the screen
He freezes and gets booted. You see because he's like all the weakest
signal I
Don't know auto is definitely a character for sure like
Well, thank you for coming out of by the way come back again sometime. That was fun. Oh, well he provided
For your psyche. I suppose it was something different for you on it
That was different. I mean he was interesting guy like I like new people to you and you know, it's like a
And I don't support that fell out with the same person that mr. Hayden was on about
I actually had a big argument with somebody over
Pawn bombing. I don't do it
There's a six inch guy
No site site. Yeah. Yeah
Listen to me. Listen to me right now. Okay. Listen to me right now. Okay?
This is my gym. He ain't shit. He ain't nobody. He's a nobody anywhere. He's a nobody
All right, you understand me, bro?
You understand me? He ain't shit. He ain't nobody, bro.
Fuck
Don't ever fucking say my name you ain't shit bro. I don't fuck me. No, I don't fuck come on bro
You know yourself, bro. You know you ain't shit come on bro. Come on bro. I know you're disgusting fire fire bro
I'm talking to Otto bro. What the fuck are you? I've never let myself down on a stream like you
Bro, shut up
I'm not some boss, I'm not some boss, I'm not some boss, I'm not some boss, I'm not some boss, I'm not some boss, I'm not some boss, I'm not some boss, I'm not some boss, I'm not some boss, I'm not some boss, I'm not some boss, I'm not some boss, I'm not some boss, I'm not some boss, I'm not some boss, I'm not some boss, I'm not some boss, I'm not some boss, I'm not some boss, I'm not some boss, I'm not some boss, I'm not some boss, I'm not some boss, I'm not some boss, I'm not some boss, I'm not some boss, I'm not some boss, I'm not some boss, I'm not some boss, I'm not some boss, I'm not some boss, I'm not some boss, I'm not some boss, I'm not some boss, I'm not some boss, I'm not some boss, I
I'm really because
over here, he's a nobody.
Okay, come back, come back later, okay?
He just wants some juice.
Wait, did he come back?
Did he say that Matt Jim was a piece of shit that you're leaving?
He's a nobody.
He's a nobody. He just wants some juice.
Why would he come back?
Just to say bye.
Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye
Yeah, that dude just wants some fucking juice fucking some juice. What fuck up, bro
You know what the fuck it is. What the fuck is that? What does that mean some juice?
Well, what the fuck bro? He wants you just wants to fucking go into it. You know what I mean? He ain't shit
I'm out of I'm fire fire
You better
You better fucking learn it quick quick
Wow
Don't wow me bro. Don't wow me bro. You better learn quick
learn
Okay, yeah
I don't come here to get a cup of juice I come here to run shit
Okay, you're gonna run shit, but it's my show. What are you gonna run shit like you show?
Like what do you mean? I
Come here to run shit psych, but it's like you show
But I run shit right here
Hey
Yeah
Say hey, yeah, I respect I respect you and everything bro, but you know what?
I'm firefighter, and I'm not no fucking lane. I know you're not
So I'm gonna run this bitch
You understand what you say
You're sure I'm gonna run I'm a fucking run something
Okay, okay, you do you?
Oh
Bro, I know you're not you're cool. I like you. All right. All right, so take it easy
Wash your hair
Make your hair pretty
Okay, because I'm not fucking run this bitch
Okay
Don't worry about it. Don't worry about it. Don't worry about it, bro. Don't worry about it, bro. You know how it is. You know what it is
You know what it is. You know what it is
Psych okay, poppy. What's up? Hey, yo, bro, you know as soon as I'm not breaking no rules
I'm not gonna let nobody step over me
Okay
You came running with your little short ass what you gotta run those short lug little legs can't run a motherfucking thing
Here yeah bend over look let me see that ball and spot so I can fix my eyeliner
Yeah, I see my reflection from your fucking top of your head you loser
You gonna go buy a leash and do what bitch?
You're my bitch. You'll speak what I tell you to speak bitch
Like you're one of those little fuckers that like to be put on a leash and dragged around and then take your fucking heels
And drag them into your balls cuz you're a bitch like that. I know what kind of trick you are. You're a pussy
So like I said, you'll speak what I say. So bye fuckers
Hi summer
Don't know. Yeah, I mean, I expect you to be able to you know, you didn't talk to her very nice
We're supposed to say you know, she's a lovely lady, right?
You know what I find it? You know what I find this sexy, but she keeps coming back
Oh
You're giving the wrong idea
She keeps coming back.
Huh?
Hell.
Okay.
Why do you keep coming back?
Your mustache is touching your lips.
Hey bro, why'd she keep coming back?
Like your mustache is touching your lips.
You know what she's doing?
She's really
Oh, no, I don't know she's trying to do that, but
You like that you like high heels on the balls you like that high heels
Yeah, yeah
Okay
That's the top of men. That's the top of men. I am they keep coming back for more. Are you slow?
No, but I am very fast and brutal
You're slow
Does that answer your question? No, you're slow
Oh, no, I am brutal to the fucking no you're not you've been
I am not to be mistaken. I am not to be mistaken for a sticker. I am not a sticker
Trust me trust me
Shut it. Why are y'all thinking?
Shut it. I am who I am and I will be brutal if I want to.
Your mustache is growing into your mouth.
Okay, well, it's not going to be your dick.
What?
It's going to be a vagina, a clit.
I ate it. I ate it. You paid for
homeless pussy. No. Yeah, you
paid for homeless pussy. No, I
was I was a very nice, very nice
dude just on the bus and he
paid for some homeless pussy.
It's okay. And it happens.
That's why you were on the bus.
That's why you're on the bus.
You were looking for homeless
I was going home and this is
This is what I don't get for being handsome. This is what I don't get.
You're balding.
Women.
You're literally balding.
You're fine, but you're dick is only six inches.
Like no.
Oh my god, am I supposed to cut off my wings?
Let's go
You gotta get like a whole fucking
Microscope just to fucking be able to find it. Oh
You know what bro, you know what I'm gonna tell you right now, bro. I
Got this thing about me. That's called charisma in real life in real life
In real life, a lot of people know me, in real life, a lot of people know who the fuck I am.
In real life, I present myself.
Nobody knows you, you're outside an apartment complex drinking beer pissing outside with fucked up hair and a fucked up fucking moustache.
And then your teeth are fucking yellow, nobody knows you.
I guess you're doing yeah, you have yellow teeth you're five foot your dick is six inches you're fucking balding
But you look like you smell I
guess nobody knows you or wants you
And you fucking take the city bus I guess you don't know what five five in London on there get somebody else do it
I guess you don't know what you're talking about.
J-Dog, now how about you come through already?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Yeah, you gotta come through already, J-Dog.
Well, J-Dog, don't get down that way.
Yeah, J-Dog, you gotta come through already.
I don't, I don't have you down that street.
I don't go down that way.
You're getting everything wrong.
Oh, I have a new street for you.
I have a new street for you.
I have a new street for you, J-Dog.
No, no, no, J-Dog.
Yeah, I have a new street for you.
No, no, no, but I got a street for auto. Yeah, but I have a new secret street for you.
I have a secret street just for you. No, no, no, there's no cameras or anything.
No, y'all need none. It's a secret street. Don't worry. I got you.
I don't need no secret street. Yeah, I got you. Yeah, we do.
But we go and we go and we go let auto go over there. I know auto wants to see what's up with that
I know auto down for that auto bro. Why don't you just shave your head, bro?
Why don't you just do like me? You know, I had that same problem you had
I was losing my shit right here, too
And I said, you know what fuck it just get rid of it man. What are you holding on to just say fuck it?
Yeah, I bet you a hundred bucks
You will look ten times better and you will pull more women if you shaved your head
Then the having whatever the fuck that disaster on your head
Can I answer you?
Yes, yes.
Yes.
Alright.
What you don't know.
What you don't know about.
Well, I don't know.
Hang on a second.
Let me answer you.
What you don't know is that is how I keep my fucking head. I buzz it. I buzz it. I buzz it
I keep myself nice and clean
కికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికిక
I'm saying you don't know me I'm everywhere people know me people know what the fuck I do people know how I keep my shit
J-Dog, J-Dog, I'm Firefire, I'm Aroh, a thousand people if you have a 6-inch dick.
J-Dog!
If not a thousand plus they know me all around here, they know they know how I keep my shit
You know why the reason why I had a run the fucking
Doing too busy for pussy ain't no man too busy for pussy man a man
Who's about his business? Man, bro, they keep themselves nice and clean, bro. They got to keep themselves locked room. Yeah
They got to keep themselves, you know looking proper, bro
How you gonna pull some people like that looking all scruffy and shit?
say yeah
If i'm gonna if i'm gonna if i'm gonna fucking be coming to your fucking home
You better fucking help these fucking people know who the fuck i am
Well explain to me explain to me auto explain to me. I'm not trying to disrespect. I I don't know you man
I don't know you. You're right. I don't know you where it's going to me
People know who the fuck I am. Who are you man explain to us who you are nobody gets a fuck who you are like you got a show
Who you are not fucking tell people like what you gotta be about not talk about it
J-Daw!
What's up?
Uh, I'm a human.
I'm a human.
I don't need to explain myself.
Raging demon?
I ain't no raging demon.
You got me fucked up.
I'm not letting 2,000 people tell you who the fuck I am.
Who?
Where are they at?
I don't know who they are.
Cause I ain't spooking on one of them motherfuckers yet.
Let me know so they can tell me.
They can lace me up.
Let me know.
You good?
Figure it out, bro. Figure it out. Figure it out. You ain't talking to no Lane. You ain't talking to no Lane
If you're trying to pull some women, why are you come up here looking like that man like you fucking
Fire fire, bro. I'm I don't well fuck you take I am you're a firefighter
Don't know I thought that I thought they had a height requirement for fire fighters, bro. I didn't say fire fire
I am fire fire
Fire fire. Okay fire fire
Better fucking learn go to one more for us ready. You say you're gonna go to Walmart
Yeah, I can make that face to auto I can make it to
You're gonna get used to me though you're Canadian I can't take you serious first of all
You know what you know what my roots is
You're lower than me, bro. You're lower than me. You clean my toilets. You clean my toilet, I mean, you clean my toilet, bro.
Oh, yeah.
What are they at, bro? What are they at home, man?
You ain't gonna fuck with me, bro.
I'm not fucking with you, bro. I wasn't trying to fuck with you. I'm just trying to get you to know who you really is.
You better get used to me though.
You better get used to me.
You better get used to.
You better get used to it though.
Don't fuck around.
I'll put you in your place though.
Put me in my place.
Oh you're five foot though.
You need five foot.
Fuck around bro.
I'm six foot.
200 pounds.
On a good day, I'm 216 pounds. That's if I eat good
I don't give a fuck bro, it's easy for me to put you in your place all the time
Put me in your place, put me in your place
I'll put you in your place
Firefighter has seen the house
Get used to it!
Firefighter is in the house
Hell yeah, firefighter
Firefighter
Where's your helmet now?
Where's your helmet?
Right now!
Where's your boots?
Get used to it!
You were a funny motherfucker, bro.
I know, you're going to be mad.
I ain't trying to be funny, bro.
But you're going to get used to me.
You're going to get used to me.
I'm getting used to you right now.
Uh-huh.
You're going to get used to me.
Watch me on that one.
I want the wild one.
Okay
This is your new locale right here. I'm gonna give him to you. This is your new locale
You know
Taking your gift no you have to take them take them on behalf of my my community to your community
You know you can maybe he might be a beautiful i don't want him on my panel
He might be a beautiful transformation. We don't know he no i don't want him on my panel
Yeah, he could you could probably give him a good makeover. You know hook him. No
I love you psych. I love you psych and he has no money. I don't want him on my in my community
I'll pay for him. I'll pay for him. Okay, then cast at me then jay. I'll give you my cash out
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Say my name bitch. Say my name. I'm gonna make you say my fucking name all night motherfucker
So I'm gonna start charging you. I must I know you used to pay and I must not charge in your bitches
And not even break a sweat
For me this is like killing time at work. This is so fun right now. It's such a locality
Fuck you talking to show me who I show me who I'm talking to little daddy
What the fuck you call me little daddy?
That's fucking lame, bro.
Show me who you are.
Show me what you work at what level, man.
Little daddy?
That's fucking lame, bro.
Yeah, little daddy.
Little daddy.
That's fucking lame, bro.
What the fuck?
Little daddy.
Yeah, you're a little daddy.
That's fucking lame.
Little daddy
Don't
Don't ever call me little daddy
All right, bitch. I'll call you a bitch. How about that? Is that better little bitch? I
Guess I guess
Charging my program. I know you I know your credit card is attached to your YouTube, but I'm gonna grab that bitch
guess I must work hard for summer right shut the fuck up I didn't tell you could
speak summer you are a very I did not tell you to speak to me no I didn't tell
you to speak to me okay now shut the fuck up and get on all four you like me
get on all if you want to be a bitch I'm a fucking be your master
Well, you need to prove to summer how much you love her you need to prove to her you're new here
So you need to prove yourself
You need to prove yourself autumn
Whatever summer says you need to do you need to answer to her
J-dog J-dog. What's cracking? Yo, is that you dog?
Hey, J-dog. Yo, I don't need to prove myself to nobody. I
No, okay, you're a firefighter. We know you're a firefighter, but you need to prove yourself here
And summer calls a shock so whatever she said you'd better do it. Otherwise you get the fuck out
Listen to me. Listen to me. You better not call me a firefighter again, ever again.
You said you were a firefighter.
You said you were a firefighter, not a firefighter.
You said you were one earlier.
And I know you want to.
And I know, and I know, and I know why, I don't know why you used, I know, I know why you used.
You said you were a firefighter earlier though.
I am a firefighter.
You said you were earlier.
You said you were a firefighter.
Fire!
Firefighter, okay. Firefighter
Firefighter
Hi everybody
Hi everybody, hello
My name is Firefighter
I love you
Firefighter
Hey, at least put on some like lip gloss or something
If you're gonna be kissing us
I mean, can I please just put some lip gloss or like some chastin?
Let's start over. Let's start over. Let's start over.
Okay.
Let's start over.
All right, little daddy.
I'm fire fire.
Hey, little daddy.
Firefighter auto.
It was cracking.
It was cracking, bro.
Hey, it was cracking, bro.
Well, you remind me of my homeboy SHP, but like an older Hispanic version, bro
You know who that is, you check him out man. He's my homie, bro. I know for a couple of years
I know, bro. He's from Denmark, man. He's a cool homie of mine. I like him, bro
He used to get drunk like a motherfucker. He got like country religion and shit. Yeah, he's married now
But you remind me a lot of him, bro. You should you should you remind me of a Hispanic SHP
You're like
I have no tone with you. I have no tone with you. I will not disrespect you auto. I will not disrespect you
Fire fire fire fighter. Okay. Fire fighter. Fire fighter. Fire fighter. Fire fighter auto
On the box, let's roll out
Hello, Kirika.
Here's the babies.
Yummy kisses.
I like yummy kisses.
You know that.
Yeah, but where though?
There you go.
Psyche just gave you one.
Give him one back.
Auto.
Don't be rude.
Psyche.
Mwah.
I'm psyche
Well now that we we discover now that we we you know you've unleashed what part of the equator you're on
We know who we know you're a switch hitter now. We know you you get down that way so flirty guy
One hour one hour one hour
I'm straight. I'm straight, but I'm confident not like yummy kisses. Yeah, you're by curious you're by curious
I mean, I mean, that's cool. If you want to be by kids, bro. I mean, I'm not gay
But you know, I need to stay I need to stay you're gonna get used to it
Okay, but you need to prove yourself you need to know that you need to prove yourself to summer
It's like we didn't let up the name and talking it's done bro. I don't
the coolest shit ever fucking
real quick. You see the
shut up. Shut up. Auto.
No, you'll listen. Well, you
did listen. You did listen.
Yeah, you won that one. I'm not
gonna lie. It's a good book.
You see the name, right?
So what was what was your question sir?
You're not talking to me. I know that I
Never have any questions
unless
Unless I'm interested
I thought somebody just asked who the fuck you let up and I'll just say my name
Are you doing auto seem like you're doing all right?
Bro, I'm okay, bro. How are you, bro? Whoever that? Thank you for asking
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Don't call me sir. You can call me out. Oh, you can call me fire. You know, I'll call you out of now on or firefighter
Call me out of bro. I'm not up your ass. It's okay. I'll call you I'll call you out of now on
All right, bro, you know me
What's up?
Who the fuck are you?
I mean, I've I said that. I'm
You come here often or what?
Sometimes not really. This is
just my second day here. So, I
don't know who the fuck. Oh,
this is just my second day here.
You're gonna let me finish talking.
This is just fucking me. I said,
Hey, shut the fuck up. This is my second day. Hello. Be nice. He's trying to be
Damn out of you. What? Who are you? Who are you? Who do you want to crash out on?
Cause I thought you'd do it. Let's do it.
Like, he's trying to be nice and be friendly.
I don't know who the Goofies are, bro. I don't know who the Goofies are, bro.
What does a Goofie mean? Okay, you made the... What is a Goofie? What's your definition of a Goofie? Go ahead.
I'm a goofy a goofy is someone
that's just gonna fucking
come on the panel and try to
fucking talk some stupid shit
because I am a goofy them
because because some fucking
real winner got on. That's a
goofy. I ain't no goofy.
Okay. So are you the next one
in line?
Oh, I am the next one. Yes, sir. I'm the next goofy. I just joined for no reason at all. I don't ain't nothing
I'm Marie. I'm kind of dumb to be honest with you
So you apologize, I don't go ahead running
Are you goofy I'm a goofy goober. I'm a goofy goober you're
All right, sit the fuck out sit the fuck down and don't yeah, I can sit the fuck like I can sit and down sir
Please auto please light just a little psyche to sit the fuck down
And shut up a I run this bitch. You know that you run it. Oh, yeah, you're
You know you're gonna so well won't you give us a little dough, you know, why don't you tell your little child little donation or something?
What do you mean donation? Why do I need to give donation? You don't need to you don't need to my presence
My presence is fucking driving
Do you understand that do you understand who the fuck is on the panel right now
Please explain because really I'm about to throw some chains because you look like you're the type of person that be something with that cup
He'll do something same for some change
Every time you talk, you don't have to say you heard. I
Know I don't have to but I am doing it you're
Yeah, every time that you talk, you don't have to make that weird a smile on the camera. You're heard
You're still gonna do it. You're heard
What the fuck, but I don't have to donate a cent bro my press you don't have to
Money bro
stupid
fuck you take it dealing with bro you dealing with nothing
you know who you dealing with you dealing with nothing but a fucking god damn fucking freedom
you know what the word freedom means
that's the face
That's the face of freedom
Like is it too early to crash out or can I crash out on you?
Go you can go and crash out you can go and crash out right now. I don't give a fuck
What are you doing on this panel bro, why don't you go to sleep?
Why don't you go to sleep?
Shout out to the don't know
Oh
Doing on the panel bro, why don't you go to sleep bro go to sleep if you're tired
Nobody said they're tired. Oh, all right. I don't use it too early
Can't hear you I'm not I need it I never get tired
Psycho
Those who don't know I never get tired. They know who the fuck I am. They know what
J-dog, they know I'm not no fucking name. They know J-dog. They know
Well, real cool. Well, nevermind.
Hello!
That's all we know about you. Although you have your five foot. You have a six inch dick. That's all we fucking know about you
You know, you know, but what do you mean? Who knows you say it was your second day here by the way
That's all you know about me local don't be a star's too logical
Lord may stars to what else I need to know about you. What else I need to know
Why you say you can last one hour, one hour?
You want one hour?
One hour?
That's what you want?
One hour.
Yeah, five bills five bills. Okay. Okay. Okay. Yeah
Yeah, I'll I stream it. Yeah, I'm gonna live stream of course
Well, fuck that since like you the fuck you're
Yeah, how are you guys doing? Yeah, we're having an interesting conversation. I think I don't know. I like this guy. Yeah, what's up? Yeah, sorry
Yeah, I kind of like
Can you teach these people how to welcome a person a real person?
You said be in the need of
There you go
Yeah, you didn't welcome me very nice either you said who the fuck am I you caught me up with these and you've been here for
New days, you're being awfully brewed. I like it. So can you teach yourself how to like treat people?
You know what I'm saying like I wasn't being disrespectful to you
Yeah, why don't you fuck it? Why don't you turn on your camera? Let's see
And what would that what would that prove? I mean, what point would that prove?
Love you. I think that would accomplish some things
When you say that could accomplish go it's like he's sorry
No, I thought I thought I thought tag backstage, but they left so I was trying to let him on but hi guys
I'm sorry. How do you check? I guess my name is Arbiter and I'm a new see and this is my first day here
And you did not accept me. You didn't accept me good at all. You're fucking shit now. I want to leave
So I'm getting bullied I feel like Otto.
Bro, leave bro, don't ever come back.
Can you apologize to me Sarah?
Bro, you know how to treat.
Otto, what are you mean for?
I had to be nice to him.
Come on. Be nice to girls, be nice to girls.
He's a good friend of mine.
Otto, stop being mean.
Alright, alright, alright.
Don't you know how to treat people, Otto?
Shut the fuck up.
Stand up for yourself, bitch.
I don't know how to see enough for myself. I don't even know how to I don't debate. I'm sorry. It's don't do that
But don't know how to argue and nothing like that. Can you please be nice? That's my point
I don't he's a little slow
Yeah, be nice to be mad I'm a little bit slow or there's a little bit slow. I mean there's what goes a little bit
Jada
What the fuck
That was me
That was a lot of fun bro. What the fuck was that j-dark? That was you auto that you auto
I'm sorry, I'm embarrassed
For you, too, man, I'm really embarrassed for you. Why are you gonna be like that?
I am so sorry. I mean, I'm I'm still waiting for an apology out of you apologize, you know, I'd really appreciate that
All right
What is your name give him a kiss to you can call me crucible ghost or a key why or Arbiter
Whatever you want, whatever you feel like
Or all three give me three apologies. I mean, obviously at this point
Okay, I'm gonna I'm gonna I'm gonna I'm gonna go with your first name. What's your first name?
Uh
Ghosts that's what usually people call me goes
You'll go
Hey, you'll go. You see the way it is around here goes is I see it. Yes. I see
The biggest dick you got the biggest
Biggest we got that's the way it goes you want to be a person you want to be a person
Be a hmm
I haven't heard an apology yet, but if you want to get to it
So that's my apology. That's my okay. Well, I like that. Well, you know, give me the respect to apologize
Yeah, you just didn't want to talk to you like that
Yeah, I would like to take this time to apologize to absolutely nobody you're fucking retarded
You don't know what the fuck you're talking about. You don't know who the fuck I am you're fucking you look like a crackhead
You sound like a bitch. You don't know how to argue. You don't have a debate
Obviously don't know who the fuck you're talking to you better fucking shut the fuck up and respect it you're
Respect respect. That's what you call a crash out auto a crack crash on I gave way more money than you don't fuck
You don't know my level sir. I never be my level sir
Matter of fact, if you'd be nice, I'd actually teach you I'd be nice and I teach you
Okay, what the fuck what? All right make your argument. Go ahead. Yeah
Fuck yeah, I don't
and let me see who I should be respecting let me see let me see well give it about
give it about three more minutes i'm sure somebody's gonna join with my picture on there
because that's what they do no stupid don't come out right now stupid no no no no no no
don't come out right now stupid that's what auto says the co-auto that's what he says
Thank you
Yeah, say it again
Exactly, I'm not going
Shut up
To learn your camp
You don't turn on your cam. No fuck you and your apology. Who are you to apologize me fuck you?
I don't care. I don't give a fuck. I'm not gonna get well
Every day every day, you're gonna feel my dick every day. That's it bro. Nobody wants to say what does that even mean?
I don't know. He's asking bro. What does that even mean? I'm gonna fill your dick every mean
What does that mean? Do you mean that like because you're trying to be insulting or you mean that literal because?
You want to make it liberal? I can make that. What does that mean? Yeah, go ahead. It means it means that you don't know what the fuck you're talking about.
It means that if you don't turn on your camera.
I ain't shooting on that camera. Don't fuck. Turn on your camera right now. Turn on your camera right now.
I'm not gonna do it. You don't fuck. Yeah, you don't fuck. Retard, I'm not gonna do it.
Do I turn on your camera right now right now what make your make your argument? Why should I turn it on?
What's your argument make an argument I don't give a fuck about your nonsense
No, I'm on the panel
This is my first time on the piano, so I guess I guess I should
Do you feel my dick
You can feel my dick which I've been on this. I've been on this panel more than you
Shut the fuck up. Do you feel my dick stupid?
Crazy demon speak when spoken to
Do you want to talk to me when I was about to talk to you?
Damn.
Damn, I don't know.
Do you want to talk to me?
Do you want to talk to me when I was about to talk to you?
Damn.
Damn, I don't know.
Do you want to talk to me when I was about to talk to you?
My man's confident
Okay
Camera that deeper my dick is gonna go into your battle
And psyche would probably grip me if I wanted you off this panel, you'd be off here
Man, bro, it's very easy to do it very
Would you like to see it happen, would you like to see it happen?
Because would you like to see that?
Nah, I believe if you think you're good, I'll go ahead.
Don't try to change it.
Get the camera on.
Sorry, I moved the call post.
I know fouls, give me sorry.
Okay. Go ahead, I'll go.
Okay then.
JT, J-Dog.
J-Dog.
What's up?
What's up, I'm not fucking I'm gonna drive my dick into this fucking thing
His name is diamond and he actually likes that
I want to be friends
Can we not be friends?
Did I not listen can we be friends sir? I don't want to why I don't think I just think I'm people
Why I guess you could be friends in sick or digging auto
You stop saying that against my will
Auto can we call you?
Yeah, big auto in this fucking house
Big auto sounds better than firefighter auto
My
Nothing to do about your dick at all
I'm gonna explain to you
I'm gonna fuck you
Did your name god damn what the fuck Jay dog do you hear that yeah man this guy's sitting
on that man did he hear that he said get on camera I'm gonna fuck you yeah he's gonna
fuck you wow how are you gonna do that how are you gonna do that how are you gonna do
that how are you gonna do that how are you gonna do that how are you gonna do that Jesus
If you don't turn your camera on, my dick is getting hard and it's going to hurt and it's going to hurt.
Oh my god.
Turn your camera on.
Why you want him so bad Otto?
Listen, if you don't shut up, I'm not gonna make the arguments
I really mackin on you like for real like noble ship. Well, yeah, he's mackin on me
Or if he really just is like he said he ain't getting now. He's gay
I'm your gays fork
Inches nobody wants to fuck with that
Inches just shut up
Hey over there
We'll be down his dick, but like nobody wants to see much. I don't put my camera and I'm gonna find out whether
Right now
Would you like to see my beautiful face, sir? How much money do you have sir white you throw psyche 20 bucks?
I guarantee I'll came up right now. So I'm 20 bucks. He why what came up you?
Come up. Yeah, those psyche 20 bucks. I'll come up. That's fair. You're not gonna fucking came up bro. I'm gonna
Fuck you. Why? Because my face is already out there.
I'm gonna be funny, bro. I'm gonna make you believe you're gonna make it.
Now you know you took now you now you took it too far, bro.
Now it's not now you're being weird about it.
You've always been weird, but now you took it too far.
Shut the fuck up. Yeah, I'm so much straight up.
I'm going to make you shut the fuck up stupid.
What the fuck would you like me to make you shut up?
It's very easy.
Hey, yo, hey, yo, J-Dog. Hey, would you like me to make you shut up sir?
So I
Matter of fact, I'm pretty sure I'm about like 300 I had pretty sure I got a couple three months in my belt make him shut up
I ain't I ain't coming up and you're gonna thank you. Thank you
Let's calm down. Let's calm down. Okay. Let's calm down. Let's calm down. Okay. Let's calm down. Let's calm down. Let's calm down. Let's calm down. Let's calm down. Let's calm down. Let's calm down. Let's calm down. Let's calm down. Let's calm down. Let's calm down. Let's calm down. Let's calm down. Let's calm down. Let's calm down. Let's calm down. Let's calm down. Let's calm down. Let's calm down. Let's calm down. Let's calm down. Let's calm down. Let's calm down. Let's calm down. Let's calm down. Let's calm down. Let's calm down. Let's calm down. Let's calm down. Let's calm down. Let's calm down. Let's calm down. Let's calm down. Let's calm down. Let's calm down. Let's calm down. Let's calm down. Let's calm down. Let's calm down. Let's calm down
They can kick you out respectfully. Yeah
Would you like me to show you would you like me to show you?
Would you like me to show you how beautiful this shit really is your
Let's do it. Let's run that bitch. You want to run it? You want to run it?
So does anybody else want to run it Goofy?
Like
Okay, just give me a little time
I did like I don't I'm not gonna argue with himself
No, man. Good. I heard you laughing. It's shit. Yeah
Man that was a character
Hey 30 seconds out of 30 seconds to be back, okay, did he told him?
Is he mad about
He's fine. He's fine. He's fine
He's a gold mine man. Keep him around
Maybe maybe I've been on panels before
Otto how was the water with the room temperature it doesn't need more ice
I mean
I'm the type of person that brings the best out of people
Okay
So I want PY to bring the best you seem like a
Okay, you seem like now fuck that I don't give a fuck about your heavenly bullshit
Like you're gonna bring the best you seem like a crash out
But guess what you met the biggest crash out you want to crash out sir. Let's fucking run it
And by the way, I'm not gonna keep I'm not gonna pay to get kicked off or nothing like that
If you want to crash out with cash out, I guarantee I'll fucking help you. I'll do it
You want to run it? We're gonna sit there and shut the fuck up
What do you mean you want to run it, bro? I want to I want to see what I sense. I'm
I'm sure hey give it a couple more. I'm sure somebody's gonna send a picture and they know what it looks like
Psych
Yeah, yeah, do you know do you know what the white looks like?
Yeah, I've seen them. Yeah, it's like definitely does what I fucking
Forget that you're new I'm sorry
I look like a thumb with a little bit of hair on it. Yeah
Yeah
An adult Haley Joe Osman, I think you know he's like a chili the guy from the sixth set, you know
He looks like the adult Haley Joe now you use the weirdo
Oh
Why you can suck my fucking balls bitch
You generate little fucking
Bro suck my balls, bro suck my balls
Bro, you asked him who he looks like, but he told you a person that you probably don't even know who it is
I said a thumb
Even if I look like a thumb, which I do look like, I look like a thumb, but I still look like you
I look like a thumb
Ey yo, are you hearing this J-Doll?
Look like a thumb bro suck my balls, bro. You suck. Hey, what's your point? I don't know
I'm mad bro chill out calm down. You came over here Mackie. No flirty diamond. I recognize
Would you like a 24-hour cuz I can give it to you easily would you like it?
Don't play around auto be careful auto
He will do it.
He will do it, bro.
Fuck.
I don't want that to do that, bro.
I run shit, bro.
I don't give a fuck.
You don't run nothing, Otto.
You don't run nothing.
What do you run?
You don't even run your own.
Wait.
Repeat yourself.
Otto, real quick.
What do you run?
You ain't running shit.
You run away from the debate.
You run away from argument.
You run away from logic.
You run away from making sense.
Any kind of sense you have.
So I do agree that you run.
You ain't running shit, Yard.
Let's have a debate and let me say you're hurt again because you didn't like that last time. Let me say that again.
Easy.
Let's have a debate.
Cripple jokes. What up?
Yo, I don't know what you're doing.
Yo, J-Go, what up, my guy?
I was cracking easy. How you doing, homie?
I'm chilling here with my wife.
You know what I'm saying?
I don't I don't I don't I don't
I don't I don't I don't
Well, honey, how are you pretty good do I call me he sees why I'm awesome
But I was like, oh
Yeah, I said I said first I'm talking to her and happy to meet her
The plane you know, you know
I hope you guys have fun have fun guys have a lot of fun. Is she from it's easy is she from New York?
Yeah, yeah, she also from New York, but she's just here. Yeah, I picked up like two
We've been getting drunk and shit, so I was like y'all watching this out the baby. So you want to join she's a matter
Damn, she can't join
Hey, hey everybody, don't get it. Yeah, I'm gonna make friends
loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco loco lo
You know what?
That goes guy
You're not gonna do that you're gonna you're not gonna
Straight up you're gonna talk English you're gonna talk about me straight up
If I want to talk to somebody in my native language, I could talk to them in my native language as much as I'm
The fuck are you gonna are you gonna if you're gonna talk about me at least
My god
It sounds like you discriminated against Latin's right now
Dude I'm about to fucking get you to
Yeah, yeah, I don't think any of us like T white T white get the fuck out. That's rude
Yeah, T. Why has the power so I would be
You don't want me here I just fucking leave you guys all
We want those here
Yeah, somebody say I let somebody pay that $25
Fucking problem T white
Okay, then pay it
The new father has arrived new father
I'll make your argument for you. Maybe you may maybe you meant to say like if it's free speech
Why would you be able to pay that would be a good? I make your argument for you, and I still out you're not gonna do it, brother
I gotta make your argument for you auto
We
And nothing you're it's not your panel. It's okay. Yeah change it. Go ahead psyche there. He's auto-changed the rules
Retard
Yeah
He donated a lot of money this week
Stupid fucking goons
Hold on. I'm not like skiing. Hold on that that bottom lip was dropping
I should with hot site. That's what I was
He's one of the producers of the show he's helps
He's goon. There's your yard. No, I'm like he's goon
What does that mean? Please? Donate a puppy. He's psyche's next top donator. You can't poppy poppy
It's like he's doing your puppy
I don't know what the fuck I'm gunning about but I guess I'm gunning
You're gonna be retarded, but you're never gonna you're not gonna out win me your ghost always wins
Okay
Yeah, thank you. Thank you. Oh, that was funny. I'm drunk. What's up y'all? Don't get don't take nine person who I'm already drunk
It's like you hit him
I'm chilling
Don't take nothing personal is the internet
Oh
I don't know if anybody saw my post but alias is a fucking cat
I don't I've never seen him, but he was on
Out of the picture I found with the badge on his neck. He's a fucking cop
Anybody want to see it you drop my link on oh my god, yes running New York is a fucking cop
Hey, yo, big pot remember that remember that a your big pond we got up in your head moon
7 on the motherfucking
My bad, I'm making rice what happened he said one eight seven
You're making rights
I thought you're making rights for like, you know, like to be no rights
Why do you have for dinner
One eight seven bro. Don't fuck around
Sikes you better make sure you better make sure there's no rats around here
You're not it. I call it not it. Not me
I'm a high profile. I'm a high
Do you think floaties cute I don't
yo no quiero ni un rato ni un
perro
no Aro, yo tengo un pronguta
pregúrate
tu que Freddy es bella
no soy muy joven
afuera
ella bella
ella bella loco
dime verdad, ella bella
ella esta linda
si o no
Talk to me
I
You know what I'll give you one favor easy
Yo auto
You think you think flirty diamonds dirty flirty diamonds cute flirty diamond change it. Um, uh, give me a big click
I'm I'm gonna answer you a best pick nothing not to do not to do um, you know exposure
But give me a best pick and let me let him give you a penny about you. I want I want to know I want to know these things
I'm a curious
All right, let me give you my best of my best of my best. I thought this bitch, right?
Crazy demon, right? Whatever crazy diamond crazy demon or whatever
She was good, bro, I thought she was good, bro, but but she has she has a set of fucking testicles
And she has a dick
I
Cannot go with that, bro. I'm straight, bro
I'm sorry
You know, you know, you know, she's still sexy, you know, you won't you won't let her bend you over like no other
Why I'm not hating on her. I love her
Yeah, I love you. I love you crazy demon. Hello
Hello, crazy demon. If you love it, if you love it, if you like it, if you like it, if you like it, you love it and you want more of it.
No, he didn't say he liked it.
No, he said he's gonna love you like all God's children should.
But there's this thing going on here.
I like lucky vagina.
So you might just backstage out of it.
You better say something smart, crazy demon.
You better not even talk to other like that, you're...
Oh, no
Yeah, we don't
Want them dumb fuck. He doesn't want them. It's not good. We're not laughing. We don't
Yeah, you better say something smart demon
Yeah, I told him I was showing my tits backstage
Cuz actually I was like playing around with it the only person I want to meet was actually you timing X. I don't like me
I don't fucking like you would you like you don't have to like why I don't like you. Yep. We'll go ahead explain
No, yeah, I don't I don't like you. I don't believe anything you believe in I think that you're so
You're so stupid, but you believe it's disgusting and here's my thing though
You like fucking flirt with men and you don't fucking get you don't tell them that you are a man
And that's
Yo, yo, go
Ask her if she got a dick all over a hundred times on one panel
She does
Well, you're not gonna make an argument for anything because you have a dick
That's my point. You told me to whip up my dick for you so you can suck on it and bounce on it
You fucking you fucking
Mother fucker say that one more say it again say it again
Who the fuck you talking to like that?
That's how
who the fuck you talking to like that?
How about that?
I said that when did I say that?
I said, yeah, come on, yeah.
When did I win?
No, stupid.
Hey, yeah.
When did it?
Listen here, sir.
When did I shout?
Yeah, come on, yeah.
You're not going to you're not going to say it because you don't know what you're all about.
When did I say?
Go ahead.
I said, yeah.
When did I say it? Please answer my question, or please fucking answer my question.
Are you gonna answer come on? Yeah, I don't know. I'm give me a chance
Why you talking shit you talking shit about psyche on somebody else's panel about how you make it money
Shut the fuck up you fucking money hating ass bitch. Yeah fuck God
Can you please come back?
Suck my dick, though. Suck my fucking dick.
I think, I think, Diamond, would you like to, I think I'm going to use a little bit of money I have left to, uh...
Yeah, suck my dick, dude.
Diamond, are you sure you just don't want to hang out?
Yeah
Diamond he has credit for kicking people out off to the show
No, why you kicked out here because
They got money they go I got a law sir
Oh, no, there's I'll sue the cops. I got money. I didn't have fun. I understand you don't have you
My wife to come over
I didn't money. I didn't want to listen. What would then listen nothing listen. I'm paying money. I'm trying to tell you something
God damn easy. You're fucking hard to talk to you. I'm trying to tell you I didn't want to talk to him because he said I was gonna come over and stuff
What oh?
You know what I'm saying like if you're gonna make that hey if you're gonna make that claim the burden of proof
I hate to be like the big brother
You're gonna make that claim the burden of proof would be on diamond year and I'm not gonna beat this is fucking like that and straight up
Now if you'd like to donate more money and have him back on and say go suck you said you're gonna suck my dick
Go ahead and do it. I'm not gonna do it. That was fallacious
He's getting all that money by the way, like I say
Like he was OD flamboyant. I would never been here
That's true
I'm kind of like
He's never once said like oh
He was too fanboy
I look
But psyche's never made that claim has
Maybe
Why the fuck all these fucking chickens crying
I
Want to suck on you they would have suck on you
You're never joined the panel hey, Glocky never do a chair
You want to be there? I will show a face. I'm like, show a face right now.
Everybody know my face. Did you not get the face? Did you not get to see the last comment?
Was that not my face?
Victor is like, a rooster has many heads.
Okay, he said rooster. I had to do it. You can't say rooster. Let your woman speak. She's talking a lot
You're a retarded crackhead homeless. We don't give a fuck
You ain't no rooster
You ain't no
Stop talking in a different language seriously, I'm one of the last warning
Stop doing that
I want you to be here
I
I'm doing good. I'm glad to hear in your voice
Ain't nobody talking to you little bitch boy. Haven't I told you you get wait for permission for what I talk to you motherfucker?
Until you get on your knees
So it's not the fuck up girls. I'm not talking to you say the fuck out of my
I
She's good peeps.
She's good. Good peeps. I don't let me tell you that when you really get to know she's
Fuck she is
She won't turn down to nobody
Yeah
You don't get kicked off the panel. That's it. That's all you got to pay money to make me go away
I don't see it in the back chat. You didn't see it. I don't see it in the back chat. You didn't see it.
You didn't see it. Fuck off dude. I already paid.
By the way, I have two more. My second one's gonna be summer.
Then I have one more after that.
We were keeping up.
Suck my dick!
Salma, you have to pay to cut me up. Hey, little midget boy
Money like the trick you are bitch
Well, I'm still here right now, I'm still here right now.
Listen, even though she's still here.
I'm still here, ain't I bitch?
Take a two little locale motherfuckers on, but I'm breaking a fucking sweat. Both of you motherfuckers could suck my dick from the back.
I'm gonna start putting some fuckin' stage two, bro.
Fuckin' bitch.
Fuckin' bitch you are, huh?
That's my presence trickin' fuzzy lay-mashed motherfuckers. I think it's beautiful.
Spray your legs. I'll eat your fucking click.
Mother, you can never touch me, you ugly motherfucker.
You're not tall enough to get to my pussy. Shut up.
Why'd you leave?
Spray your legs, bitch.
I'll eat your fucking click.
Oh, my gosh, motherfucker. Shut up.
Yeah, what are you doing?
Well, I'm doing that tonight, baby.
Yeah!
You should be off the panels for the time of your life. I'm just saying.
So fucking safe
You know what you're talking about shut the fuck up whatever your name is receive a hair line shut up
You ankle might are looking mother fucker shut up
Well, they'll never do anything over here you're nasty you're disgusting shut the fuck up
Thank you for watching.
Like, yo, bless it be the holy water.
All the sun, all the spirits.
Okay.
Ghost, where'd you go?
Ghost left.
Why do you leave ghost left?
Ghost left, I don't know.
He doesn't spend some money to shut me up
because that's the only way he's going to shut me up
is to fill money like a low-cow turkey is.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm eating your pussy and I'm going to burn sage
Shut the fuck up motherfucker, shut up
Go chase her, receive an hairline
Them motherfuckers running all the way backwards
I'm eating your pussy
Shut up, you're not doing nothing
Go do a lot of cocaine and smoke some cracks
Shut up
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Because you look like a fucking kiddie that you already are.
I'm a kiddie.
You look like a fucking kiddie that you already are.
And this bitch used to get laid and I'm gonna fuck her.
She's not a hank.
No, she's the caretaker. She take care of you.
She take care of the roosters.
You know what? I think she's not a hank.
I think she's just a fucking duck bitch.
She is a beautiful lady and I love her. I love her for what she does. No, no, no, no. Fuck that. She is an amazing lady. God bless her.
God bless her. I respect her, Papi. I respect her. On that, that's the one thing me and you might not agree on one day, you know?
I respect Summers. I respect her and I respect what she does. She is a beautiful lady.
Who the fuck are you? Who the fuck are you? Why are you talking to me? Why are you talking to me? Who the fuck are you?
Yo, to tap us out.
Don't talk to me. I don't give a fuck. Don't talk to me. Yeah, some is a beautiful lady. I'm gonna keep on saying that
I'll slice you up right now, bro. I'll slice you up. I'll keep
Alright bitch, you want it?
Alright bitch, let's go.
What's up bro, I'm the rooster.
I'm the rooster around here.
I'm the fucking rooster.
What do you got?
What the fuck is wrong with you? I'm the rooster out here.
I'll fuck all hands.
Who's wrong with you?
You see that you see this pussy boy. You see this pussy boy talking all that shit and then he says oh
No, where you at? Where you at papa? You look like you in the cage right now. You mom. You might be the rooster
You look like you in the cage
What the fuck is that background?
Where the fuck you at?
Look at your fucking mustache. How the hair goes over your fucking lip. You look stupid
All right, that's your fucking mustache. Save your fucking hair
Get the fuck out the cage you look like you in champ in the hole
You show you ain't shoving that phone up your ass
Can you show you in that in jail with papa and your phones in your ass and you tucked it in front of CO's papa
Are you doing the red D?
కికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికికిక
You want to start, you want to start, you want to start, you want to start, you want to start, you want to start, you want to start, you want to start, you want to start, you want to start, you want to start, you want to start, you want to start, you want to start, you want to start, you want to start, you want to start, you want to start, you want to start, you want to start, you want to start, you want to start, you want to start, you want to start, you want to start, you want to start, you want to start, you want to start, you want to start, you want to start, you want to start, you want to start, you want to start, you want to start, you want to start, you want to start, you want to start, you want to start, you want to start, you want to start, you want to start, you want to start, you want to start, you want to start, you want to
I'm the rule
Hold on guys, hold on guys, hold on guys, okay
I'm gonna shut up. I'mma shut up.
by the way, right? Hey, okay.
What if I twist you like a
They me so far how about that? How about that?
You listen bitch, I'll rule you bitch
Hey site site. Yeah, hold on take it. So good. How long is summer time down for yes?
Well, at least for the I mean, I don't know
Go stop acting like you ain't gonna be on summer's panel in a week or two. Stop
Stop now
Take that summer shit back right now
For it next time not this time. What's your problem? What's your argument?
I'm telling you
Dropping
I'm just taking a point. I know you paid for this idea. I know you didn't pay for it.
Okay, then shut the fuck up. I don't care about your argument.
My precious, my precious.
Well, I actually make one. I should be careful about it.
My precious. That's why I thought it. That's why I thought it.
Are you the Phyllis police? Make an argument. Are you the Phyllis police?
No, because I believe in free speech.
But you're not going to come at me. You know better.
I don't know better. You know better. You do better. I'm black
The only place you're gonna be able to fucking go live on is here
Remember just now cuz you will be banned every place I like so I like psyche. What's wrong with
and that that ghost and why are you sir actually you might be there why are you here but psyche
so the only place you're gonna see is ghost right now psyche is bad we shouldn't be here correct
you're in black and white we shouldn't be here well if summer's going on summer's better psyche's
bad we shouldn't be in psyche you're done you're done you're done you're done you better pay
How about that now? Now you're done. Now you got to pay like every dollar you can to speak online because now
People's gonna be blocking you to make you pay double
I
What panel
No, no, no, exactly. So what's your fucking argument, sir?
I think your argument
I think your argument was like you're going to pay me
Listen, how about this? How about this?
The camera is going to come for you as fast as you can
Go ahead
So you don't know what you're talking about me, sir
He does said that I'm gonna make him pay twice more than me, but have you seen our dollars?
Well, they're way more than that, but go ahead
Because we can summer come back dump goes when can summer come back within the 24-hour period tell me
No, she's running out. She's running that fucking mouth. She's on one night. Okay. Well, it's okay. Well, I think he'll
I think good night good night. I'll see you later. Okay
I
Okay, he left he left. Okay, that was the
Join the conversation. I think we should all three talk me and
Summer okay summer. Do you want to come back up here? Summer? He said you can come back up and
From the community goes yes, it's there just about to be
God bless you for making a right there from what go ahead and bar. What are you in a army from what? What are you talking about?
Bro, we weren't strong enough community. You know, everybody in our community fucking each other. What do you mean? We you're saying me
I'm not part of your community. I got one community, bro. Like you fuck with one. You fuck
Is my time out done
Okay, you come back up it's over with some of it's over
She's gonna run her fucking mouth 24 hours
Go ahead, I'll give you a chance
That my timeout is officially over with
No, it's not you you have a chance to talk like mean
Yeah
Psychi 24 hours
I'm sure my final decision.
Yeah.
Don't fuck yourself.
You will fuck away.
It's all the way.
You're going to get anything that's taking your way through.
That's very that's that's very nice of you to say that.
Yeah.
24 hours.
Let's make psyche some money tonight.
Sorry.
I don't want to I don't listen sir. I don't want to
You're kind of retarded honestly, you don't have to fucking
Hey kicking you off you fucking dumb mother fuck you got no argument your bum ass nigga you fucking talk with your eyes closed
But got it. Okay. I got you. I got easy. Let's be cool. What how many times I get to speak cool guys
Let's free speech me cool. Hey. Hey, nigga
Fuck that pay to kick me off right now. Hey to kick me. All right. You're gone
Do that. Do that. Do that. If I could go bust another my fucking bitch right now
Yeah, you're good. Okay. I paid 20 for the next one. I guess I got five more. Yeah
I don't want to kick anybody free speech
We can talk about whatever you guys want to talk about as long as I don't break a psyche spaniel to a spinoff
Okay
Yeah, well, that's pretty crazy man
Okay, well you yeah, yeah, okay, so
Yeah, because you okay, okay, so can she said she'll talk just never said she'll be nice because you come back
She said she'll be nice. I'm dumb. I said I paid no I'm fucked up. I'm done. I'm done with somewhere. I'm done
I'm done. No, I gave her how many what's like you how many will answer this question for me
How many chances I give her I just said like listen just be cool. She was crashing the fuck out
Which is okay. It's okay to crash out
She's crashing the fuck out on me and I said this please calm down
I said it's free speech. You can say whatever you want as long as you don't break cycles panel
You're fine to say whatever you want and she's still crashing on me
Did that not just happen and then I gave her the 24 hours or am I crazy?
It's like yeah, you know what psyche it's your panel
But yeah, but she comes back
But if she comes back if I say she's gone will you let her go?
We is she gonna be on?
Okay, well, yeah, I'm giving you I'm giving summer chance. I like summer. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay
Okay, we say like if I say she's gone. She's gone. Correct. It's not fine
Okay, so yeah, they'll see
There you go. Yeah, I agree with that if she wants to agree to argue
So wait a minute. So so now is my time off done because I'm not gonna crash out
But I need to know that my time limit my time out is over. No
Since she's here it's there that she's here now she's here now. No, all right
No, no, okay, you're here now
Yeah, because my timeouts over with so thank you
No, I don't want it though. I don't want it and I paid a lot of money for I don't
I'm not crashing out
Okay, but the timeouts over that I'm not crashing out so chill the fuck out now she took you know what I did for her
I gave her that privilege. You know what she did. She immediately like said like oh
I'm not there anymore. No what was said was like one word for me. You're gonna be back
Just agreed on that
Timeout's over with motherfuckers, so guess what?
Ah, bitch, now you're stuck with me.
No, you're stuck, no, Jackie, no, she's, she's, no, 24 hours.
No, because you don't get to do that.
I gave her a chance, I gave her a way, I gave you even one more.
No, you don't get to do that.
You brought me, you brought me back.
You brought me back.
You don't get to do that.
You want me gone again?
I didn't, I didn't bring anybody back.
By the way, you said since I'm here, you said since I'm here.
You said since I'm here, you said since I'm here.
You said since I'm here, then my timeout's over with.
So holler!
Like yeah, I told you one word, right?
No, he said y'all need to work it out cuz you're making it too confusing you did that not him
Likey
You should know
Everybody no, you can't control me
Because he kept his end of the bargain up so you can try again, but sorry sucker
Come on dude
I'll give you
Hey, I'll give you the boot back and you can't boot summer because you already brought it back twice and now we're back on it
So I'll give you the I'll give you back your boot, but you have to use on somebody else. Okay. You can't use it on summer again
He's a water back twice, you know, and so it's like I think that's like
He's going to pay it again, I bet you I put money on it. He's going to put me
He's going to get some more money to time me out
Hey, thank you. I helped with that fun computer. I hope you get a good one, baby
It has come in and choose so LES and choose what are you here?
Here we go guys
Man, y'all niggas over there spending that paper man shit. I got we got I got a host open panels too man
Y'all go on come over and spend that bread man. I think if they're spending stacks and shit
So how does this work
He needed a new computer I made sure he had enough money to get a good computer for so that's what's up
That's what's up now. Tell me how this works over here. So a nigga got a penny fifty bones
Alright
And then in the channel by summer, it's in the channel description. Oh, okay. Okay. Yeah, choose. So it's in the channel description
The rules, okay, so there's that that's how it works. It's not $50 for everybody. It's it's a straight $25 cake off
Okay, so anyway, yes, and I am
Guys and the new computer is really gonna help out the show too because they'll be like
I'll be able to do a lot of cool things that I'm not able to do now with the computer
So it leads my microphone. I have a professional microphone all kinds of stuff
I have VR I can do maybe on stream and stuff. So it'll be cool. It'll be cool. How's everyone doing?
You won't be a content creator we benefit from this shit man. Get paid in a room with it
And it goes I'm giving you back your boot. I'm giving you back one of the boots
But I just said you can't use it on summer. Okay, you need back one of them, okay?
But you can't use it on summer today because you because you're just gonna change your mind about her and it's like
And I really don't feel like just kicking her off over and over again. So
Okay, so
If you don't know that dude, you know, you know that dude was slow, man
Know that dude was slow
But he's slow though, he don't you don't get what he can't
You know what he's doing like he's paying money to have niggas put it in the back
But didn't come back five minutes later leave him up
Like really mean ghost actually fuck with each other right yeah, I did that but he's slow though. I mean, oh well
Like like sharp bus helmet slow jewel at the mouth slope. I don't know what he's doing that do probably got a handler
I just I want I want those to be able to go
I wasn't even coming after you guys. I was going after that guy that little short syndrome fuck a Chihuahua dude
I was going after him, but then you stuck your nose in it
So then you got that ass because one thing for certain and one thing's for sure
I'm always gonna cook a bitch. I'm always gonna win know that so you
I'm going after somebody else
Okay, yeah, and
But and uh, yeah, so we're here. Here's goes back. Here's goes and goes
I know you really like summer and I also know that you want to be on the talk your ish and you know
And it's a whole her show too. So I don't want to like you guys had a problem
No, that's not a problem. I uh, I had a problem with that paid a lot of money and like
Like I don't want to kick someone I don't want to do that
get some of your chances to come back, but I wasn't going after you. I went after the guy that went after me all day, and then you came up here and interfered. Yeah. And so you made it about you. I was never going after you though. I apologize.
James, do you accept Christ as your Lord and see?
I'm not talking to you, but some are y'all
Because he was coming after me all day we've been playing with him all day long and then you came in
I guess I didn't know enough of the information to understand that and I apologize
Yeah, that dude slows my last nobody say
But psyche if I want to kick someone I should have the ability to do it
I know but I'm staying with summer. You know you keep wanting your back
And so I'm like hey, I'll just to give you back. I know I do they used to her okay
Yeah, and I want you to like I don't want you to be on bad terms. I want her everybody be happy here
I know you're on good terms with her. So it's like let's just continue being friends. Okay
The part of the game
She said was just sure but if I do spend the money and I want somebody kick
Listen, I didn't pay to bring you back. I paid to kick you back
Hey
Leave them in time. You can't recant your statement. They let them back up somewhere. I timed her out. That means you wasting your money. I'm saying you wasted your money.
They're not making at this point. He's like he's a hypocrite. We don't look like we're talking about that.
No, I'm saying if you're spending your money timing things out, bro, you got it. You can't, you can't recant.
Yeah, it's been all this money and I'm not even getting what, I'm not even getting what I'm saying.
You have to bring them back. You have to bring them back. You have to bring them back. You have to bring them back, ghost. That's the problem.
No, I'm the person. Let me talk.
I was respectful. Will you let me talk like he's that fine?
I was I was respectful enough not to summer actually at this point
I was respectful enough to be like yeah, she was just talking shit
I love summer. Please let her back up. And then you said yeah, you want her back up?
I was like, no, she's sorry. But I said but what I said, I'm sorry to get you sorry to yell
But what I said was like, yeah, but if I say one word, you're gonna have to hear again, but like
She's crashing out. She's crashing on me. Like, oh, she's not up here. She's totally cool.
She's not now, but that's what has to do with her.
I'm being like, oh, you better stop before I start crashing out. Stop, stop, stop.
I almost saw money back here.
Summer you won't find that's white one, but that's besides the point
I don't know man. I have the money. All right. Do you know what? I lost money because I was being respectful
Salute salute
I was like, yeah, let her back up here like don't let her on the panel. We'll let her talk to me
I get you back here
Would you say sorry
Summer has to take toes
It was hot today, I had to braid my hair
Do I get out of your nose?
No, see how you left me.
You know you left me.
Here's the problem though, I do love you a lot.
And I was like, yeah, let her join, let her join.
Well, I said let her join, too.
But I wasn't going after you.
I wasn't, that didn't really time,
I wasn't going after you.
I was going up to the little fucking store,
dude, that's what they call me, a bitch all day.
Okay, what about me and my money and my time?
Nobody talks about that.
Well, but you don't know me.
know me about now if I'm cooking and you jump in you go get hit by a stray bullet for sure
and probably like and if I if I donate it to kick you off wouldn't that be like
yeah to hear what you have to say because I like you I don't want to kick you
okay well I'm back and I'm not cooking you right now so what are you doing why are you
I'm gonna turn the fuck it's go on
Let's all get along right now
I'm giving you I agree you're back here boots you can use it, but I said not on summer because I don't you already time
You're out and brought it back twice and so I wouldn't like just to give it to you
I think I think that but not tonight
You and then you spend more money, but he's not doing that. He's saying okay. I see what's happening
So let's not do it to summer anymore because I was like that
It's like a year they're gonna you're gonna give me my money back or your respect you're gonna respect
That's fraud
That's fraud, by the way.
I'm having so much fun today. This is great. I love it. Yeah, you're having fun on my expense, but what you
It's twenty five dollars to kick somebody what's
When you kick someone they can't come back
Okay, I think that you can go back
Not over $20 that it goes I really want you to be
Okay, well fucking we love it. We love you really love it. We can run it. We love summer here
We love summer here. We love summer and we
I'm giving you back. I'm giving you back
You really want to run it because I everything's recorded by the way new age, but do you want to run it?
I'm here to take your order. I'm
going to get paid for a refund
because I'm going to get paid for all
that shit. No, you're right.
Oh, yes, I do. Yes, I am.
Ghost you're gonna make me cook you and then you're gonna get bad and then you're gonna go
I'm going to take your order.
No, what I'm gonna do is I'm gonna get paid
No, you're not. I mean I am I am gonna get paid
No, you're not because we have the videos and he can easily prove that he is
See this way you don't know how to talk
I'm trying to be nice. I'm trying to be nice about your day, ma'am. I don't I didn't ask about my day. I said, how was your day fruit loop? I
Don't I don't give a fuck. Did you ever hear that? I don't care. I don't give a fuck. I don't give a fuck
Don't you do what do you want to answer that question buddy? He probably like
My face I bet goats would love that
Okay
$25 I'm gonna kick somebody and you you offered those services and you didn't give it to me when I paid for that money
How's that?
I
Refunded I'm not refunding. I'm I'm giving you that
You can use it on somebody else I said, okay
People are listening to better for it. You see the banner. Look at the banner. Look at the banner.
Look at the banner. Look at the banner. Look at the banner. Look at the banner.
I don't give a fuck. It's too late, brother. You're going to lose. I swear to God, you're going to lose.
Brother, come on.